<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MindSpark</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>


    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="module_title_structura">Structura</string>
    <string name="module_title_dynamus">Dynamus</string>
    <string name="module_title_silicus">Silicus</string>
    <string name="module_title_voltus">Voltus</string>
    <string name="module_title_substantia">Substantia</string>
    <string name="module_title_accelero">Accelero</string>
    <string name="module_title_ideam">Ideam</string>
    <string name="module_title_robustus">Robustus</string>
    <string name="module_title_fascinus">Fascinus</string>
    <string name="module_title_illuminati">Illuminati</string>
    <string name="module_title_prodigium">Prodigium</string>
    <string name="module_title_cognitio">Cognitio</string>


    <string name="event_title_epitome">Epitome</string>
    <string name="event_title_conquet">Conquest</string>
    <string name="event_title_metropolis">Metropolis</string>
    <string name="event_title_id_civil">ID Civil</string>

    <string name="event_title_assemblix">Assemblix</string>
    <string name="event_title_id_2d">ID 2D</string>
    <string name="event_title_id_3d">ID 3D</string>
    <string name="event_title_mechtrix">Mechtrix</string>
    <string name="event_title_turnament">Turnament</string>

    <string name="event_title_code_junkie">Code Junkie</string>
    <string name="event_title_code_junkie_pp">Code Junkie++</string>
    <string name="event_title_xterminate">Xterminate</string>
    <string name="event_title_retracer">Retracer</string>
    <string name="event_title_predict_x">Predict-X</string>
    <string name="event_title_hackathon2.0">Hackathon 2.0</string>

    <string name="event_title_circuit_fixer_1">Circuit Fixer I</string>
    <string name="event_title_circuit_fixer_2">Circuit Fixer II</string>
    <string name="event_title_encrypto">Encrypto</string>
    <string name="event_title_microapps">MicroApps</string>

    <string name="event_title_on_the_etch">On The Etch</string>
    <string name="event_title_dexters_lab">Dexter"\'"s Lab</string>

    <string name="event_title_wheelomation">Wheelomation</string>
    <string name="event_title_the_wright_turn_glider">The Wright Turn Glider</string>
    <string name="event_title_the_wright_turn_rc_plane">The Wright Turn RC Plane</string>
    <string name="event_title_aqualympics">Aqualympics</string>
    <string name="event_title_contraption">Contraption</string>

    <string name="event_title_byldan">Byldan</string>
    <string name="event_title_ppt_comp_it">PPT Comp/IT</string>
    <string name="event_title_ppt_mech_prod_meta">PPT Mech/Prod/Meta</string>
    <string name="event_title_ppt_eei">PPT EEI</string>
    <string name="event_title_ppt_civil">PPT Civil</string>

    <string name="event_title_search_n_destroy">Search N"\'" Destroy</string>
    <string name="event_title_robowars">Robowars</string>
    <string name="event_title_dog_fight">DogFight</string>
    <string name="event_title_bot_wrestling">Bot Wrestling</string>
    <string name="event_title_virtual_robotics">Virtual Robotics</string>

    <string name="event_title_the_amazing_race">The Amazing Race</string>
    <string name="event_title_bull_run">Bull Run</string>
    <string name="event_title_bidzkreig_1">Bidzkreig 1</string>
    <string name="event_title_bidzkreig_2">Bidzkreig 2</string>
    <string name="event_title_lan_slam">LAN Slam</string>
    <string name="event_title_flash">Flash</string>

    <string name="event_title_chakravyuh">Chakravyuh</string>
    <string name="event_title_indikya">IndiKya</string>
    <string name="event_title_torquest">Torquest</string>

    <string name="event_title_genius_jr">Genius Jr</string>
    <string name="event_title_sudoku">Sudoku</string>
    <string name="event_title_googler">Googler</string>

    <string name="event_title_ham">HAM</string>
    <string name="event_title_tux">TUX</string>
    <string name="event_title_stareway_to_heaven">Stareway To Heaven</string>
    <string name="event_title_cnc_lathe">CNC Lathe</string>
    <string name="event_title_virtual_labs">Virtual Labs</string>


    <string name="event_objective_epitome">This event presents how the classroom formulae of shear force and bending moments, Castigliano"\'"s Theorems, take shape. This event provides an insight into structures and their behavior in different circumstances. The teams need build a structure based on the problem statements using the given materials.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_conquest">Concrete is an inevitable part of any type of construction. This event requires designing concrete cylinders which are able to sustain maximum tensile load, which is one of the major load acting in any structure</string>
    <string name="event_objective_metropolis">Our country, inhabited by over 1.3 billion people, is amid a massive transition from rural characteristics to urban characteristics. India is urbanizing rapidly offering great opportunities to build a new nation, while facing challenges in sustainable urban growth. It is a huge task to manage increasing population pressure on existing urban areas and to provide decent quality of life to the residents. This can be achieved by creating a Utopian Society that leverages technology, utilizes existing and planned infrastructure and promotes economic, social, environmental changes through our theme ‘Towards Techno-Utopia’. City planning deals with the concept of “smart-city”- the ability of a city to develop at the highest level, the potential of the citizens and of its resources towards achieving a collective well-being i.e. quality of life. Districts are where people live and make decisions about key city systems, such as transport and energy consumption. The main challenge in this priority area is to reduce Environmental impact, and work in areas of Community planning (slums), Infrastructure (physical and social) and Transportation. This will require managing and integrating all the smart services and comprise a city’s ecosystem in areas such as the environment, energy, urban mobility, leisure and administration. Metropolis is a platform for young generation to give afuture development plan for a given problem in an innovative manner considering the above factors. The problem statement will be made available 20 days before the start of MindSpark’17. Participants are required to study the problem statement and find an innovative solution to the problem. They should prepare sheets (A1 size) and write a report which explains their idea and a 3D model (selected participants) which depicts their solution.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_id_civil">‘A good designer is who caters to the need at hand but a great designer is who does that in a unique yet feasible way.’ In a developing country like ours, this is what is needed, simple yet workable solutions. Like its said ‘There is no such thing as a boring project. There are only boring executions.’ Do come forward, show your skills and intelligence in planning and designing your own buildings.</string>

    <string name="event_objective_assemblix">Assemblix will test your ability to understand assembly drawing and production drawing. It also tests the team’s knowledge regarding mechanical components. Teams will be required to assemble components together to make a machine part with or without its drawing.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_id_2d">The key to perfection of a product lies in its perception. A flawless drawing is an engineer"\'"s most important tool of perception. Similarly, it is equally important that the drawing is according to the actual manufacturing technique. Sharpen your software skills and gear up to face the challenge!</string>
    <string name="event_objective_id_3d">This event tests your skills in 3D designing and modelling. Show your ingenuity at designing to become “Champion of Intelligent Designing”.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_mechtrix">This event tests your ability to make use of every available resource in an optimized manner while racing against time. It gives you a chance to explore yourself and bring out a creative and innovative spark to create something from junk i.e. “Jugaad from Kabaad”. Brainstorming, innovation and fun, MECHTRIX has it all. So, put on your hat of creativity, get ready to dirty your hands and let the “Junkyard War” begin.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_turnament">Unleash your machining skills, and let in to the groove of screeching rhythms of turning, facing, tapering and all you can do in a lathe club.Want to perform operations on the lathe machine?? This is the event where you can show your workshop practices.Participants are required to perform a set of operations on the job using lathe machine for which problem statement will be declared on the spot. The competition of producing a mechanical component given in drawing by using lathe machine.A work evaluation is done based on the surface finish, time required, and dimensional accuracy.</string>
    
    <string name="event_objective_code_junkie">The objective of this event is to test the students’ knowledge in basic C Programming. This event is for beginners and intermediates, and will try to cover general aspects of the C programming language.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_code_junkie_pp">The objective of the event is to test the knowledge and innovativeness of students in object-oriented programming. This event is for programmers having some experience in OOP and will try to cover object-oriented aspects of C++, Java and Python programming language. The event has been designed for people who love coding and who are passionate about programming.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_xterminate">The objective of this event is to test the participants code understanding skills, i.e. how you interpret a given code and work on it.Code-writing and debugging skills will also be tested; writing codes that are easy to comprehend is an invaluable skill.The language used will be ‘C’.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_retracer">Retracer is an event that tests participants’ ability to find out the hidden logic behind apparently disconnected entities. This event allows the participants to make the full use of their thinking capabilities to get to the results quickly yet carefully. It is an event for those who go beyond the traditional approach of identifying 4 as 2 + 2, 3+1, 4+0, and so on.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_predict_x">Do you have what it takes to create artificial intelligence, challenge dumps of data and create meaning out of it? The field of data science is evolving into one of the fastest-growing and most in-demand fields in the world. Predict-X will test your ability to understand data, analyze it, and build predictive models and execute Sentiment Analysis. We challenge you to solve real world problems with all your data science skills.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_hackathon2.0">This is a 24-hour hackathon to code, strategize and innovate some ingenious solutions to the most sought out real-life problem statements.</string>

    <string name="event_objective_circuit_fixer_1">Test your skills in the field of basic electrical and electronic circuits.Apply your theoretical knowledge and practical skills to conquer this event.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_circuit_fixer_2">Main objective of the event is to test the theoretical and practical knowledge of students in various fields of Electronics and Electrical Engineering.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_encrypto">This event is all about digital system and circuit designing. The technical aim will be to come up with simple ideas based on Digital Systems Design to protect a given place/object from any form of unauthorized access. Participants are supposed to design a fool-proof electronic system based on the problem statement given (Innovative Systems that can be used by the common man e.g. Housing Security System, Corporate Security or various detector and control circuits such as fire and smoke detector and extinguisher). Consider every parameter and aspect of break-in points and reverse engineer your efforts to detect and eliminate flaws.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_microapps">The theme of this event is ‘Towards Techno-Utopia’using technology to progress towards a perfect world!’. The event aims at finding innovative solutions to current real-life problems through the competitive nature of the event. The objective of the event is to test how well versed the students are with the microcontrollers, the ability to think ‘out of the box’ and their ability to solve and design innovative systems for given problem statements with regards to real life constraints.</string>

    <string name="event_objective_on_the_etch">On the Etch is an event which provides a platform for the students who are passionate about metallurgy and materials science to present their metallographic skills. Not only metallographic skills but also the practical thinking and logical reasoning ability of the participants will be tested in the competition. The main objectives are as follows: \n 1. To test the metallographic skills of students for sample preparation. \n 2.To test the logical reasoning ability of students by observation of microstructures of metals and alloys. \n 3. To make students explore more about the metallic parts used in day to day life and in industry at large scale and to explore their microstructural features by thinking broader at “Micro” level. </string>
    <string name="event_objective_dexters_lab">The objective of the event, Dexter’s Lab is to provide a platform for the students who are passionate about chemistry and its practical applications. The event will test the basic knowledge of chemistry along with the practical skills of participants. It may involve general questions about recent events involving chemistry and its use in the world of technology and Human Welfare. Practical skills and knowledge of Acids and Bases is your savior in this competitive lab-event.</string>

    <string name="event_objective_wheelomation">This event involves the fabrication, testing and racing of a wireless remote-controlled, 4 wheeled, IC engine powered vehicle.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_the_wright_turn_glider">Apply your knowledge and manifest your engineering skills to build innovative gliders.Also, compete yourRC planeto find the most agile aircraft.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_the_wright_turn_rc_plane">Apply your knowledge and manifest your engineering skills to build innovative gliders.Also, compete yourRC planeto find the most agile aircraft.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_aqualympics">The various aspects of engineering enable humans to travel over water. This event requires the participant to design a remote controlled (RC) boat and maneuver it through difficult obstacles.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_contraption">Conservation of energy and mass are two rules which govern the universe. This event is designed towards converting energy from one form to another and driving a series of events which will ultimately carry out the given task. The more complicated the contraption, higher the points earned.</string>

    <string name="event_objective_byldan">The idea for this event is to harness the builder, planner and most importantly the creator within. Using these qualities, the teams are to propose a city.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_ppt_comp_it">To provide a platform to young engineering youth for presenting their out of box, unconventional and innovative solutions. Also, a chance to develop stage daring and presentation skills.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_ppt_mech_prod_meta">This event essentially is a small conference where research conducted by students in the recent past is presented.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_ppt_eei">To provide a platform to young engineering youth for presenting their out of box, unconventional and innovative solutions. Also, a chance to develop stage daring and presentation skills.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_ppt_civil">To provide a platform to young engineering youth for presenting their out of box, unconventional and innovative solutions. Also, a chance to develop stage daring and presentation skills.</string>

    <string name="event_objective_search_n_destroy">Search N Destroy is basically a line following and maze solving competition. A track of white line on black background and/or black line on white background will be laid out with codes placed at some places and an autonomous robot has to follow that line, decode the path based upon that code and complete a task.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_robowars">In this mortal combat, reach to the top by being the last bot standing. Crush your opponent because only the fittest will survive.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_dog_fight">As our dream is to go towards the Techno Utopia and as we know that the wireless communication is the major part of it, the objective of DogFight this year will be to create a virtual communication network and transfer the message of success.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_bot_wrestling">Bot Wrestling is basically a competition of two wireless robots competing in an attempt to push the opponent out of the arena. These robots must be remote operated.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_virtual_robotics">This competition tests the designing skills of the participants, wherein they present original ideas, which, if given the right platform, can transform our day to day lives.</string>

    <string name="event_objective_the_amazing_race">This is a competitive treasure hunt designed for the tacticians and strategists. It involves a series of clues which lead the participant from one location to another. Quick thinking and problem solving abilities are required in this event. The teams must compete to be the fastest by solving the clues and finding next locations.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_bull_run">A stock market simulation event to test your skills as an investor and stock trader. As live market conditions are simulated it will require the participants to use analytical skills in order to correctly choose the companies to invest in.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_bidzkreig_1">Put your analytical skills to test and select 15 players to create your own cricket team. A limited sum of virtual money will be allotted to each team for placing bids. Each player up for bid will be attributed with specific points and a fixed base price. The team with maximum cumulative points will be the winner.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_bidzkreig_2">This event will test the analytical skills to test and select 11 players to create your football team. A limited sum of virtual money will be allotted to each team for placing bids. Each player up for bid will be attributed with specific points and a fixed base price. Players up for auction will be from current leagues of England, Spain, Italy, Germany, France, Netherlands and Portugal.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_lan_slam">Think of yourself as the master of CS:GO, LANSlam gives you the opportunity to prove that you are better than others. Here you compete against the likes of yourself, who consider themselves the best. Fight against them to prove your dominance and emerge victorious. \n Role of Terrorists: Plant the bomb in all rounds and/or eliminate the opposing team in all rounds. \n Role of Counter-Terrorists: Prevent the terrorist from detonating the bomb in all rounds or eliminate the opposing team in all rounds.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_flash">Photography is an art of observation. It has little to do with the things one sees and everything to do with the way they see it. Do you think you have the sight of keen observation? If yes, surprise us with your images by participating in the categories that suit you the best. No restrictions on the number of categories you want to participate in!</string>

    <string name="event_objective_chakravyuh">This is an Open General Knowledge Quiz. Questions will be on History, Current Affairs, Business, Technology, Culture, Music, Politics, Sports etc. This is an open quiz; everyone can participate.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_indikya">Indikya, the National level India quiz, is the most recent addition to Mindspark. It will test the true patriot in you as the questions in the quiz will be based on everything related to India be it sports, history, politics or even geography! The event will be conducted in 6 cities (excluding Pune) with winner from each city round will be invited to Pune where they will be up against 6 teams selected from the city round held in Pune for 6 berths in the Final.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_torquest">This is a SciTech Quiz. The quiz tests the knowledge of the participants in the fields such as pure sciences, applied sciences, gadgets, mathematics, engineering and everything else that’s included in SciTech. Emphasis will be given to Popular sciences as the quiz is intended for the general audience. Hence, students from streams other than Science are encouraged to participate. A few questions from Prelims and Finals will be based on the MindSpark’17 Theme: “Towards Techno-Utopia”.</string>

    <string name="event_objective_genius_jr">The aim of Genius Junior is to provide insight for school students into the world of engineering. It will require the full extent of their aptitude, skill and knowledge to solve the questions. Genius Jr. will be conducted across Maharashtra in 14 different cities.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_sudoku">An event for sudoku enthusiasts to come show-off their skills in solving complicated sudokus faster than anyone else.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_googler">“Google” is the world’s most powerful search engine and a step towards “Technical Utopia”. Do you have the ability to utilize it the best? Here is our challenge to make everyone aware of the power of GOOGLE and also to test their technical as well as general knowledge. Find out how many questions you can make Google answer for you.</string>

    <string name="event_objective_ham">The workshop covers the basic topics in Communications Engineering.HAM radio is a way to talk with people around the world without any sort of commercial network connection. It also includes working on Radio Frequency band and building home brew experimental circuits.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_tux">Since ancient times, the human race is inventing and discovering new things. Sharing one"\'"s knowledge is what has led to the development of a civilized society. But nowadays, most of the knowledge is being patented. Knowledge is no more “freely accessible”. Can we revive the freedom of knowledge of the past to create a better future?\nTaking steps in the direction of “free” knowledge, are various Linux User Groups (LUGs) and ‘free and open source’ (FOSS) groups.\n“TUX” is one such effort taken by COEP, to spread the philosophy and knowledge of Linux operating system and other free and open source software.\nAim of the workshop is to make people familiar with Linux and getting them started with contributing to free and open source software.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_stareway_to_heaven">“Google” is the world’s most powerful search engine and a step towards “Technical Utopia”. Do you have the ability to utilize it the best? Here is our challenge to make everyone aware of the power of GOOGLE and also to test their technical as well as general knowledge. Find out how many questions you can make Google answer for you.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_cnc_lathe">COEP is one of the few colleges in Maharashtra that has CNC LATHE machines. The aim of this workshop is to educate the participants about the working of this widely used commercial machine, which will definitely help them in near future.</string>
    <string name="event_objective_virtual_labs">1. Raising awareness about the Virtual Labs initiative- a group effort by the top 8 IITs along with CoEP.\n2. Improving access and effectiveness of the available learning resources.</string>


    <string name="event_structure_epitome">Round 1: \nMultiple Choice Questions
        \n\n Round 2: \nThe qualified teams should make a structure for the problem statement within the given time using materials provided by the organizers.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_conquest">Three concrete cylinders should be casted from M40 Grade mix of age less than or equal to 28 days on the day of the event. Winners will be decided by taking average of tensile strengths and weight of three cylinders and the short quiz about mix design. Cylinder should have maximum split tensile strength and minimum weight. Maximum split tensile strength and the maximum score in short quiz about mix design will be considered as particular for winning criteria.
        \n\nDesign Specifications:
        \n Design and Cast 3 concrete cylinders of size having diameter 150mm and length 300mm.These specimens will be tested at the age of 28 days for split tensile strength and weight.
        \n\nQuiz Specifications:
        \n Short quiz will be based on mix design and use of natural fibers in design.
        \n\n MATERIAL PROVIDED FOR MODEL MAKING.
        \nCutter
        \nSand Paper
        \nHigh Density thermocol (10mm) Normal thermocol (10mm)
        \nFevicol
        \nPins
        \nSponge sand (green, red, brown,yellow)
        \nForm/ card board
        \n30 cm scale
        \nTinted sheets (green and brown)</string>
    <string name="event_structure_metropolis">Round 1: Sheets and report submission.
        \n(Only top ten finalists will be selected for second round)
        \n\nRound 2: Model making round.
        \n\nRound3: Visual presentation through sheets, Model, 3D view and Drawings
        \n\nFormat:
        \n\nReport Writing:
        \n• Minimum No. of pages- 20
        \n• Typed report and printed on standard, white A4 size 8.5*11inch paper.
        \n• Font size- 12.
        \n• Style- Century
        \n• Spacing- Single.
        \n\nSheet:
        \n• Minimum 3 and maximum 10</string>
    <string name="event_structure_id_civil">Round 1: This round consists of submission of abstracts (Time 3 hours). Problem statement will be provided on the day of event.
        \n\nRound 2: This round involves execution of the problem statement on AutoCAD. Based on the evaluation from Round 1 and Round 2, participants eligible for 3rd round will be selected.
        \n\nRound 3: Prepare a presentation explaining the brief logic behind the design and why you did what you did.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_assemblix">Round 1: Multiple Choice Questions with only one answer. MCQs will be based on the basics of Machine Drawing, blueprint reading and your knowledge about machines.
        \n\nRound 2: You will be given an assembly drawing or its exploded view and your task will be to decide the optimized sequence to assemble the mechanical components.
       \n\nRound 3: Assembly of a given machine"\'"s sub-assembly.
        \n\nDetails:
        \nRound 1 will test your ability to understand assembly, production drawing, mechanical components and workshop knowledge.
        \nTeams qualifying from Round 1 will be shortlisted for Round 2. In this round, qualified teams will be provided with the assembly drawing. The teams then will have to give a proper sequence to assemble the components of a given assembly with specifying time required for each step as well as the instruments required. Further the teams will be shortlisted based on their performance.
        \nTop 10 teams will be allowed to attempt the Round 3.
        \nIn this final round, drawing may or may not be provided. This task needs to be completed in a pre-specified time. Teams have to use their knowledge and their abilities to join the given parts and complete the assembly.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_id_2d">Round 1: Multiple Choice Questions or Single line answers.
        \n\nRound 2: Drawing the orthographic/ isometric view of the given view (AutoCAD software).</string>
    <string name="event_structure_id_3d">Round 1: MCQ round based on general knowledge of 3D software.
        \n\nRound 2: We will give the orthographic views of the parts. Participant need to make a 3D model of every part and assemble it.
        \n\nRound 3: We will give a topic and the participant needs to design and make a 3D model of the system.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_mechtrix">Round 1: MCQ round (no elimination).
        \n\nRounds 2 and 3: Complete the given task using the materials provided by the organizers. There will be elimination after the second round based on the combined points of 1st and 2nd rounds and the shortlisted teams will compete in the final round for the title of the MECHTRIX CHAMPIONS.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_turnament">Round 1: Quiz paper
        \n\nRound 2: Making the given job on lathe (Simple Job)\t(15 -18 teams)
        \n\nRound 3: Making the given job on lathe(Complicated Job)\t(5 teams)</string>

    <string name="event_structure_code_junkie">Round 1: \nThis round will consist of multiple choice questions. The time limit will be 30 minutes. Negative marking will be implemented; details for which will be disclosed at the time of the event.
        \n\nRound 2: \nThe top teams from Round 1 will advance to this round. This round will be conducted in the campus and in different slots. This round will be a rapid coding round where the output file needs to be submitted and will be judged. Teams will be given a set of questions to be solved within a stipulated time. How fast the team builds up a working code will be considered. Scoring scheme will be disclosed at the time of event.
        \n\nRound 3: \nThe top teams from Round 2 will advance to the finals. This round will be a speed coding round and relatively tough questions will be set up. This time, the teams will have to make the code both working as well as efficient. All the possible inputs and corner cases shall be handled. According to the time taken to submit the code along with the efficiency of the code, the teams will be judged.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_code_junkie_pp">Round 1:
        \nIt will consist of multiple choice questions with single correct answer. Participating teams could take the test from only one of these 3 categories:
        \n\n1) C++
        \n2) Java
        \n3) Python
        \n\nMaximum 100 questions could be attempted by a team.The marking scheme will be announced on the spot. This round will be conducted online, but in our campus. You will be provided access to the test only if you report at our event venue during the allotted time slot.
        \n\nRound 2: \nThis round is a puzzle round. Some tricky problem statements will be given and participants will have to find out the solution within a given time. More details will be disclosed on the spot to the qualified teams.
        \n\nRound 3 (Final):\nThis round will be a proper coding round and relatively tough questions will be set up. This time, the teams will have to try to make the code both working as well as efficient. All possible inputs and corner cases shall be handled. Judging criteria will have great emphasis on execution time and memory usage of the programs.
        \nMore details will be disclosed on the spot.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_xterminate">Round 1: \nThis round will consist of multiple choice questions. The marking scheme and time limit will be announced on the spot.
        \n\nRound 2: \nEach team will be given two problem statements. Within the time specified at the event, you will have to find the solution. Points will be given based on the approach and to the number of programs solved.
        \n\nRound 3: \nEach team will be given two sets of problems.One set will have programming questions and the other set will have debugging problems. We will provide two computers to each team. One computer will be used for debugging and other will be used for programming. Each participant will be assigned one computer. For the debugging problems, we will give you codes with logical and syntactical errors and the teams will be expected to correct all errors. In this round, team members will have to swap places after regular intervals of time (the duration of which will be specified at the time of the event). Each participant will be allowed to work on only one problem at a time, and the next problem will be provided only after completion of the current problem.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_retracer">Round 1: \nThis round will consist of multiple choice questions. Participants will be asked to identify patterns in the given problem inputs and outputs and choose the governing algorithm or code snippets from the given options. The teams with maximum number of logically correct answers to MCQ’s will proceed to the next round.
        \n\nRound 2: \nTeams will be allotted problem statements containing program input and their respective output. The teams will be asked to develop their own programs to solve the problem for any test case. The judging criteria will be time required to produce error free code as well as the code efficiency. Participants are expected to follow good coding practices.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_predict_x">Predict-X will consist of a single problem statement split into two sections, fundamental and technical. Participants will have 30 days to solve these problems. During the 30 days, the participants must register and submit the solution in the form of a code and a solution set that will need to be uploaded.
        \nPredict-X will present its participants with datasets and a blank solution set which will need to be filled as per the output of your written code. Predict-X wants to challenge your ability in scanning and analyzing data and hence it will have no programming language restrictions.
        \n\nJUDGING CRITERIA:
        \nJudging will be based on the correctness of solution and code review. Both sections have a decided mathematical marking scheme which will be followed to rank the submitted solutions. In case of a tie the code review will be considered. An accurate solution with an absurd code will be disqualified and considered as cheating. Provided accuracy in solution and code, participants will be judged on the efficiency of the code and its ability to be generalized for other similar problem statements.
        \n\nDETAILS:
        \nPredict-X consists of just one round split in two sections, fundamental and technical. The event will be conducted online and has no programming language restriction. The context of the datasets needed will be provided. The expected format of the solution, code and reference and mining of the datasets will be explicitly mentioned. The event will be conducted on Hacker Rank under the name Predict-X. Registration and submission of code must fall within the 30 days of its existence. Using any reference material while solving the problem is allowed, but copying code from other contesting teams will be deemed illegal.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_hackathon2.0">Problem Statement Declaration:
        \nThe overall problem statements will be released by 14 August 2017, Monday. A few more details will be released a week prior, around 9 September.
        \nParticipants will have to choose one problem statement from the options offered. The overall problem statement will contain a basic idea of what the participants will be working on.
        \n\n24-hour Hackathon:
        \nAll the participating teams will work round-the-clock on their chosen problem statements for a period of 24 hours, starting at around 4-5 pm on 16th September.
        \nAt the end of the allotted time, the teams will give the final presentations in-front of the judges.
        \n\nDate: 16th and 17th September 2017.
        \n\nTime: Teams will start working around 4-5 pm on 16th September and will be expected to have a complete working solution by 4-5 pm on 17th September.</string>

    <string name="event_structure_circuit_fixer_1">Round 1:This round will consist of Multiple Choice Questions based test.
        \n\nRound 2:In this round, practical knowledge of basic electrical and electronic circuits of the participant team will be tested. The time limits will be mentioned on the day of event (Details about it will be given on the spot).
        \n\nRound 3:In this round, individual teamsneed to implement the circuit according to the problem statement given.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_circuit_fixer_2">Round 1: Quiz round with Multiple Choice Questions
        \n\nRound 2: Subjective-type questionnaire in which teams will be asked to solve questions within a set time limit.
        \n\nRound 3: Problem statement will be provided to teams which qualify from Round 2. Teams will have to design a circuit to solve the given problem. This round will be judged by experts.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_encrypto">Round 1: This will be an MCQ round testing the participants’ basic knowledge of Electronics and System design.
        \n\nRound 2: This round will test the logical reasoning ability of the students in the field of Electronics and System design and give optimal solutions to cryptographic problems. Students will have to answer questions in descriptive manner and if required draw circuits explaining their answer.
        \n\nRound 3: Shortlisted students will have to go through a viva taken by one of the college faculty.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_microapps">Round 1: Microcontrollers, you think you know them?
        \nA written test will be conducted with objective type questions and a few subjective questions as well. The questionnaire will be based on the basic theory of microcontrollers and its applications. Basic knowledge of microcontroller units (timer, ADC, DAC etc.) and its peripherals is required. Other details regarding the duration and marking scheme will be disclosed at the time of the event.
        \n\nRound 2: Are you "\'"Code-blooded"\'"?
        \nTop teams from round 1 will advance into this round. Participants will be tested for their C coding skills and logic. The microcontroller that will be used is from MSP430 family of Texas Instruments or Arduino. The IDE will be Code Composer Studio (CCS). Participants will be introduced to the microcontroller as well as the IDE by experts.] prior to the commencement of this round. Internet facility is also provided. Details regarding problem statement and rules will be provided at the time of the round.
        \n\nRound 3: Can you think \'Out of the Box\'?
        \nFinalists selected from round 2 will advance into this round. They are required to analyze the given problem statement which will be based on the theme ‘ Towards Techno-Utopia’ and come up with innovative and optimized solution. Design of the solution should include both hardware and software aspects. After the design, the teams will have to implement it successfully within the stipulated time. All the material required for implementation will be provided by the organisers. Teams will be assessed based on their way of approach and understanding of the problem, justification for how their solution is consistent with the theme of the event.
        \n\nEvaluation procedure will be disclosed just before the commencement of this round.</string>

    <string name="event_structure_on_the_etch">Round 1: It is a metallographic quiz which comprises of 40% weightage of total evaluation.
        \n\nRound 2: This round consists of making and presentation of microstructure of the sample followed by small question answer session with judges. This round comprises of 60% weightage of total evaluation.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_dexters_lab">Round 1: It will consist of objective-type questions related to basic chemistry and its application.
        \n\nRound 2: This round will test your practical skills. In the practical round, participants will be expected to perform certain simple experiments in provided time limit. Experiments will be explained before the concerned rounds. Accuracy and precision in results will be given priority.
        \n\nRound 3: This will be a viva round, where your knowledge will be tested by the experts in the field.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_wheelomation">Abstract Details: The abstract submission is mandatory and is intended to give us an idea about the effort put in by the participants. The abstract must include close up photos of your empty chassis, steering system and suspension system. Even if your car is incomplete, do send your abstracts. It helps us to make sure that ready-made machines are not entertained in the qualification round.
        \nRound 1: Qualification Round:
        \nThis round will consist of time trials. Two laps are to be completed one-by-one. The best lap time will be considered and relative ranking will be done accordingly. First 16 teams will be shortlisted for the next round.
        \n\nRound 2: Elimination Round:
        \nTop 16 teams from first round will be selected for this round.
        \nA modified track shall be disclosed at the time of event and each team will get a copy of all the details of the other teams and all teams will be given 15 minutes to analyze the track. Each team beginning from rank 1 will get a chance to challenge any team. Any team can reject a challenge only twice, except when the team is being challenged by a team ranked lower than it. If the challenge thrown by a team is rejected, the next ranked team gets the chance to challenge any team.
        \nIf a challenge is accepted, a time slot will be given to those teams and the match will be conducted. In this round, after the challenge, all the 16 teams race with their respective competitors and the 8 winning teams will be promoted to the next round.
        \n\nRound 3: Same procedure of challenging will be followed after modifying the track in Round 3. At the end of the third round, the 4 winning teams will be ranked according to the time in which they complete the race.
        \n\nFinals:
        \n1. The finals consist of 4 matches: Semifinal 1 and Semifinal 2, followed by 3rd place playoff and the Mega final.
        \n2. Semifinal 1 will have 1stvs 4thwhile semifinal 2 has 2ndvs. 3rd.
        \n3. The losers of the two rounds will face each other for the 3rdplace playoff.
        \n4. Mega Finals: This will feature the winners of Semifinal 1 and Semifinal 2 battling it out to be crowned as the “CHAMPIONS of WHEELO”.
        \n\nTHE LAST DATE FOR ACCEPTING ABSTRACTS IS 16TH SEPTEMBER 2017.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_the_wright_turn_glider">Part A: Make your own Glider
        \nIn this round, you have 30mins to make your glider. We will provide you the required materials (cardboard, scissor, glue, cutter, tape) and a basic design of glider will be available. However, you are allowed to bring your own design which would be beneficial for you.
        \n\nPart B: Test Flight
        \nIn this round, each team will have 3 chances to fly their gliders. Out of 3 trials, best air time will be measured. Points will be awarded for air time, flight and design of the glider.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_the_wright_turn_rc_plane">Round 1:
        \n\nPart A: Inspection Round
        \nIn this round, the plane will be tested for its design and safety constraints.
        \n\nPart B: Test Flight
        \nModels successfully clearing the inspection round will be given test flight. Teams will be judged for the functionality of their model and flying skills.
        \n\nPart C: Theory of your design
        \nExplain the logic and science behind your design and how it flies.
        \n\nNOTE: Those who are not able to fly their aircraft, judges will help them for their test flight.
        \n\nRound 2:
        \n\nPart A: Innovation
        \nSolar RC Planes, Miniature Planes (which can be used for surveillance) and make minimal noise, etc.
        \n\nPart B: Practicability(Why should my plane be deployed?)
        \nApplications such as aerial photography, monitoring(agriculture, construction sites, wildlife and poaching), search and rescue operations, military applications, delivery of goods and medicines etc.
        \n\nPoints:
        \nThe marking scheme will be notified on the day of event. Top priority will be given to take-off and landing, application and innovation. Points will also be awarded to clearing the checkpoints and performing aerobatics.
        \n\nArena Description for RC planes:
        \n1. Take off Zone – 10x1.5m
        \n2. Qualification line – 8m ahead of Take-off Zone
        \n3. There will be certain checkpoints consisting of poles arranged in a specific manner which will be notified on the same day.
        \n4. Bonus points will be rewarded to aerobatics performed by the RC plane. These aerobatics may include vertical loop, horizontal loop, barrel roll, stall turn, inverted flight etc. Landing zone – square of 5m side</string>
    <string name="event_structure_aqualympics">Round 1: Every boat must complete 3 rounds in the arena. The RC boats with the best lap time on the course will qualify for the next round. The number of teams that qualify for the next round will depend on the number of participating teams in the event.
        \n\nRound 2: The qualified RC boats will then face balloon obstacles along the course. Any boat that touches a balloon will be penalized by adding 2 seconds to their lap time. Similarly, any boat touching the walls of arena will be penalized by adding 3 seconds to their lap time. The RC boats with the best lap time on the course will qualify for the next round. The number of teams that qualify will depend on the number of participating teams in the event.
        \n\nRound 3: This will be the final round with a minimum of 2 obstacles i.e. balloons and plastic balls. Any boat that touches the balloon and plastic ball will be penalized by adding 2 seconds and 1.5 seconds to their lap time, respectively. Similarly, any boat touching the walls of arena will be penalized by adding 3 seconds to their lap time. Now there’s a twist, being the fastest is not enough, points will be allotted for the circuit and design. The winner will be declared based on both the speed and the design.
        \n\nNOTE: There might be additional rounds with added obstacles depending on the number of teams participating.
        \n\nSpecifications:
        \n1. Maximum length of Boat: 30 cm.
        \n2. Maximum width of Boat: 20 cm.
        \n3. Height has no restrictions but participants are recommended to keep it below 25 cm.
        \n4. Participants are free to use any materials of their choice. Recommended materials are light weight wood (balsa), Styrofoam, or plastic corrugated sheets.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_contraption">Problem Statement:
        \nSEGMENT A:- You have to open the DOOR of house. The door can be hinged anyway as you want and the material of the door can be a cardboard or thermocol.
        \n\nSEGMENT B:- As soon as door opens, A BURGLAR ALARM should ring. There is no fixed time duration between opening the door and ringing the alarm.
        \n\nSEGMENT C:- In the last segment, there will be a human profile (THE THIEF) standing at certain distance(not less than 1 feet), with the help of some energy conversion you have to projectile a small stone/solid material which will fly in air and it strike the thief . This is the final task that you have to accomplish i.e. "BEAT THE THIEF".
        \n\nROUND 1:
        \nThe first round consists of abstract submission (soft copy).
        \n\nLast date of submission of abstract is midnight of 15th September 2017. You can send it on our email ID: contraption@mind-spark.org
        \n\nContraption Design (200 words): (The overview and theme of contraption design)
        \n\nROUND 2: Depending on the abstract teams will be short-listed for round II which will be the qualification round. All teams are expected to get 4 copies of the printed abstract for the event, clearly mentioning steps and chart, which shows all Energy conversions. (If possible, diagrams should be added.)
        \n\nSCORING PATTERN:
        \nA– Completion of first task. (180 marks)
        \nB– Completion of second task. (120 marks)
        \nC– Points for theme related steps. (Depending on steps, Decided by judges)
        \nD– Neatness, tidiness and overall look of contraption model. (out of 50)
        \nE– Use of mechanical, chemical and electrical energy. (15 for each)
        \nF– Total repeated mechanical, chemical and electrical energy. (3 for each)
        \nG– Total energy conversions except mechanical, chemical and electrical. (15 for each)
        \nH–Total repeated energy conversions except mechanical, chemical electrical. (5 for each)
        \nI– Total number of energy conversions. (15 for each)
        \nJ– Number of compulsory steps, bonus steps used. (20 for each)
        \nK– Points for abstract representation, simplicity, presentation or explanation of contraption at the time of event and behavior of team.
        \nL– Points deducted due to hand touches. (30 for 4 hand touches, 60 for 5 hand touches, 120 for 6 hand touches)
        \nM– Points deduction due to failure in initializing two parallel lines at the starting.
        \n\nFormula used:
        \nZ=180*A(A=1)+120*B(B=1)+C+D+15*E+3*F+15*G+5*H+I*15+20*J+K-L-M Note: -Points for [C, D and K] are given and decided by judges.
        \n\nBonus steps:
        \n1. Display of message promoting " TOWARDS TECHNO-UTOPIA"
        \n2. Use of non-conventional source of energy.
        \n3. Conservation of energy during the contraption (e.g.: switching off any appliance used, etc.)
        \n\nTHEME RELATED STEPS:
        \nThis year\'s theme is \'TOWARDS TECHNO-UTOPIA’ Towards a technologically ideal world\'.
        \nTechno-utopia is an ideology based on the idea that advancement in science and technology could bring about utopia.
        \nTry to incorporate the steps involving the use of the things differing from the existing one in work, design. (e.g. using a bulb as a heat source)
        \nYou can claim points for such steps and if the judges found it appropriate then you can earn up to 30 points depending on the steps used.</string>

    <string name="event_structure_byldan">Round 1: This will be an online round. All teams will be allocated a fixed budget and land areas. They will be required to purchase amenities for the system from the given credit. Evaluation will be done on the basis on how well the constraints have been held up keeping practicality in mind (we are still working on a systematic way for expressing more creative inputs like flying cars and so on).
        \n\nRound 2: This will be the be the final round. Each team will be provided a full imperial sheet on which they must provide a pictorial representation (block diagram acceptable) of their city plan. The teams are allowed to use only the inventory from the previous round.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_ppt_comp_it">Round 1: Participants should submit the abstract of their paper to team Mindspark17 via email. The email IDs are provided at the end of each event.
        \n\nRound 2: Participants should submit their paper to the judges and give Power point presentation of (10+2) minutes, explaining the details of their research paper.
        \n\n1.CREATIVITY OF COMPUTERS.
        \nCreativity is very difficult, perhaps even impossible, to define in objective terms. Creativity amongst us manifests itself through a lifetime of sensory cues and experiences. Can, and to what extent can this ‘creativity’ be developed in an AI even after feeding it large data sets of existing sources of creative and non-creative material. 2.IMAGE PROCESSING AND THE “SEE” OF OPPORTUNITIES. A picture can speak a thousand words. From photoshopping your pimples, OCR, metallography, to military grade satellite imagery, this visual form of data is literally changing the way we see the world. How is (and can) image processing, picture restoration, color computation and all the new fields change the things we do today, and the way things will be done tomorrow?
        \n\n3.ETHICS FOR PLATFORMS.
        \nEver growing platforms like Facebook, the majority share of social media know everything about you. Your private messages (WhatsApp), statuses, photos (Instagram) all pass through its servers. To what extent can we trust the personal data of billions of people in the hands of these giants? The right and wrong of targeted advertising, suicide trend alerts, taking down ‘offensive’ posts and more are up for debate.
        \n\n4.THE INTERNET OF THINGS.
        \nDrones to be used for taming cyclones! Shopping carts that are ready to bill even before you reach the checkout counter. IoT, the fastest growing concept today. Let us hear your radical ideas of how you would change any of the existing concepts, the working, its applications, its future…
        \n\n5.EDUCATION FOR ALL.
        \nMeritnation, NPTEL, MOOCs, Open Internet exams. Maybe as a reference for textbook answers, as a supplement for that really boring class or as a course that you ‘minored’ in during your summer. How is eLearning changing our outlook towards education? Is it actually imparting equivalent knowledge vis-à-vis the brick and mortar institutions or does it lag behind?
        \n\n6.CRYPTOGRAPHY.
        \nWe have all seen ‘Imitation Game’. Cryptography although a Mathematician’s game can now barely be done without the assistance of supercomputers. In today’s world, advancements and security scenario how does cryptography fit in?
        \n\n7. Any other topic of your choice (related to the theme of MindSpark’17) will be accepted.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_ppt_mech_prod_meta">Round 1: Submitted Abstracts will be reviewed by the Event Head
        \n\nRound 2: Review by relevant faculty members
        \n\nRound 3: Selected papers will be presented at the event by students</string>
    <string name="event_structure_ppt_eei">Round 1: Participants should submit the abstract of their paper to team Mindspark17 via email. The email IDs are provided at the end of each event.
        \n\nRound 2: Participants should submit their paper to the judges and give Power point presentation of (10+2) minutes, explaining the details of their research paper.
        \n\nTOPICS
        \nSMART, EFFICIENT ENERGY GENERATION AND TRANSMISSION
        \nA. Maximum Power Point Tracking (MPPT) for solar panel system or wind mill systems
        \nB. Smart Grid Energy Systems
        \nC. Energy efficient ‘Electrical/Electronic Power Management and Transmission system’
        \n\nSUSTAINABLE ENVIRONMENT FRIENDLY TECHNOLOGIES
        \nA. Energy generation from waste plastic, water, etc.
        \nB. Reduction of E-waste
        \nC. Use of Thermo Generators for Increased Efficiency and Eco-friendly Generation
        \n\nSOCIETY AND TECHNOLOGY
        \nA. Disaster warning, response and prevention systems
        \nB. Technology in agriculture
        \nC. Innovative technologies in law and order
        \n\nROBOT AND INTELLIGENT AUTONOMOUS SYSTEMS
        \nA. Robots for precise, arduous and hazardous industrial/ domestic/ military tasks.
        \nB. Satellite and aerospace technology
        \n\nNote: Apart from the above mentioned, any topic of your choice which is in accordance with the theme of MindSpark’17 will be accepted.
    </string>
    <string name="event_structure_ppt_civil">Round 1: Participants should submit the abstract of their paper to team Mindspark17 via email. The email IDs are provided at the end of each event.
        \n\nRound 2: Participants should submit their paper to the judges and give Power point presentation of (10+2) minutes, explaining the details of their research paper.
        \n\nTOPICS
        \n1. INNOVATIVE MATERIALS/TECHNOLOGY AND PRE-ENGINEERED CONSTRUCTION
        \n· Pre-engineered Construction.
        \n· Fast Track Construction.
        \n· New Age Formwork.
        \n· Automation in Construction Industry.
        \n· Eco-Friendly/Green Construction Techniques.
        \n· Innovative Materials
        \n· Demolition of buildings
        \n· Nanotechnology in construction
        \n\n2. TRANSPORTATION AND GEOTECHNICAL ENGINEERING
        \n· Urban Traffic Planning and Management
        \n· Intelligent Transport Systems
        \n· Metro/BRT/Monorail Projects (benefits and feasibility).
        \n· New construction technologies/Designs for Pavements.
        \n· Case studies on Geotechnical Investigations/ Advance Foundation Techniques.
        \n· Accidents/Failure studies - Causes, Prevention, and Remedies. Applications of Geo-synthetic and other materials in Geotechnical Engineering
        \n\n3. ENVIRONMENTAL AND WATER RESOURCE ENGINEERING
        \n· Green and Ecological Technologies for Urban Planning.
        \n· Measures to Improve the Deteriorating Air Quality.
        \n· Environmental Township Planning
        \n· Environmental Impact of Dams
        \n· Innovative Ideas for Treatment of Water.
        \n· Flood/Watershed Management
        \n· Economic Utilization of Water Resources.
        \n· River Linking.
        \n\n4. PROJECT MANAGEMENT
        \n· TQM in Construction Industry
        \n· Project Risk Assessment and Management
        \n· Cost Control techniques.
        \n· Supply Chain Management.
        \n· CPM/PERT Networking in construction of major projects
        \n· Construction Claims Management
        \n\n5. STRUCTURAL ENGINEERING
        \n· Advanced Pre-Stressed Concrete Structures.
        \n· Earthquake resistant structures
        \n· Bridge Engineering
        \n· Fiber Reinforced Concrete
        \n· Self-Compacting Concrete.
        \n· Ferro cement Reinforced concrete corroded columns
        \n· Analysis of Durability of High Performance Concrete using artificial neural networks
        \n\n6. SURVEYING
        \n· Land Surveying.
        \n· Hydrographic Surveying Methods and Applications
        \n· GIS, GPS, and Remote Sensing Techniques
        \n· Setting out Methods for construction Projects.
        \n· Preparation of Survey Maps and Digitization.
        \n· Project data Generation based on Topographic, Soil, Water, Geological, Archaeological, Socio-Economic Surveys
        \n· Surveying Software Applications 37 Computer and Information.
        \n\n7. Any other topic of your choice (related to the theme of MindSpark‟17 ) will be accepted</string>

    <string name="event_structure_search_n_destroy">Task:
        \n1. Teams must build an autonomous robot which can trace line, decode the code and make turning decisions as directed by the code and finally push the box in the space provided.
        \n2. There will be checkpoints placed at certain locations for repositioning of the bot in case of hand touch.
        \n\nNote: The event to push box by robot and making it to deposit in the gap by is termed as destroying of opponent’s territory. The robot should not physically damage the wall and the box.
        \n\nSpecial features: There will be a binary code painted on some parts of the track. The code consists of 3 black/white squares placed in a line perpendicular to the track. The side of the square will be equal to the width of the track. The code will decide whether the bot has to take a left or right on the upcoming cross shape track or ‘T’ shape track. The “intelligent” bot is expected to read the code as it moves over it and decode it, to find out the next direction to go. Correct decoding of the code and hence the correct path tracing will earn you points. The actual code at the time of competition will be revealed only after the competition starts. (i.e. after dry run).
        \nThis code-decoding part is an innovative part of the competition designed for the challenge takers. Following the code will fetch you more points than simple line follower. So, if you think you can make an “intelligent” line follower bot, you can design considering the code.
        \nHowever, the team can go ahead with a normal line follower bot and still can take part in the competition.
        \n\nArena:
        \n1. All dimensions are in mm.
        \n2. Maximum dimensions of arena will be 4000 x 4000 mm.
        \n3. Width of track will be 30 mm.
        \n4. Dimensions of start zone is 200 x 200 mm
        \n5. The floor of arena shall be made of wood (plywood) and finished with vinyl sheet. Do not assume the floor provides a given amount of friction.
        \n6. Participants shall not assume the track is consistently white or the floor is consistently black. Fading may occur.
        \n7. The track may contain discontinuities at certain places.
        \n8. The dimensions of the arena would be accurate to within 5% or 20 mm bidirectional.
        \n9. Do not make any assumptions about amount of sunlight, incandescent light or fluorescent light that may be present at the contest site.
        \n10. Dimension of Box will be 100 x 100mm.
        \n\nMACHINE SPECIFICATIONS:
        \n\nDimensions and Fabrication:
        \n1. The machine should fit in a square of size 200x200 mm. There is no height limit.
        \n2. The autonomous robot must be stable and must stand on its own at the beginning of the run when put in the starting point. Robots not fulfilling this criterion will be disqualified.
        \n3. During the run, the autonomous robot can expand itself provided it does not damage the arena in anyway. However, the machine should not leave anything behind while tracing the path. The machine should not scratch, damage or destroy the track or accompanying parts of arena.
        \n4. All bots found damaging the arena will be immediately disqualified. The final decision is at the discretion of the organizers.
        \n5. The teams are allowed to use ready-made sensor kits. However, they are not allowed to use Lego kits, ready-made microcontroller boards or any similar assemblies.
        \n\nPower supply and propulsion:
        \n1. Machine must be completely self-contained and should receive no outside assistance. It should not use an energy source employing a combustion process.
        \n2. Machine should have an on-board power supply. No external power supply is allowed.
        \n3. Potential difference between any two points on the machine should not exceed 24V DC.
        \n\nScoring system:
        \n1. Taking correct decision as dictated by the code: 20 points
        \n2. Passing certain checkpoints will earn you 10 points each. They are indicated in the figure.
        \n3. The placing of box carries 30 points.
        \n\nTie breakers:
        \nIn case of a tie of scores between two teams, teams will be given preference based on the following criterions in the given order
        \n1. Minimum time taken by robot to cross same number of checkpoints.
        \n2. Minimum number of hand touches.
        \n\nCertificate policy:
        \nCertificates will be given to all the teams.
        \n\nTeam Specifications:
        \n1. A team once registered, cannot register again, even with a different name.
        \n2. A team may consist of maximum 5 students.
        \n3. A team may consist of members from different educational institutes.
        \n\nNote
        \n1. NO power supply will be provided during match. However it can be provided for battery charging purposes.
        \n2. There will be no provision for computer, programmer, IC, etc by the organizers.
        \n\nARENA:
        \n\nArena Details:
        \n1. ‘White color filled circle’ In arena denotes Checkpoints
        \n2. All dimensions are in mm
        \n3. ‘BOX’ In arena shows the code
        \n4. Dimensions of small rectangle (9cm *9 cm)
        \n5. Black color filled circle’ In arena shows point fetching checkpoints
        \n\nCode Details:
        \n2 Bit code:
        \n10 : Left Turn
        \n01 : Right Turn
        \n11 : Forward
        \n00 : ---
-</string>
    <string name="event_structure_robowars">1. Each match will be of duration 5 minutes and winner will be decided based on certain criteria.
        \n2. The winners of the qualifier matches will be declared as per the points they would achieve in the matches.
        \n3. Format of matches (Knockout or League) will be decided depending on the number participating teams
        \n4. There may be a possibility that in a special case there may be more than 2 teams competing in a match
        \n\nSpecial Cases are as follows:
        \n1. If there is a tie of scores between more than 2 teams.
        \n2. If the number of participating teams do not fit within the desired format.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_dog_fight">TASK 1)
        \n• MR has to pick up the Base of Powerhouse and place it in the Power Zone.
        \n• Then MR has to place the Head of Powerhouse on the base of the Powerhouse (inside the hole).
        \n• Task 1 is compulsory, and AR can start only after completion of Task 1.
        \n\nTASK 2)
        \n• MR can proceed to pick up the towers (one at a time) and place them in the Tower position.
        \n• Tower switch can be placed on its position only after the placing of tower in its position.
        \n• At the same time, AR can push any 3 boxes in collectors other than the one marked with yellow border.
        \n• After putting the 3 boxes, the last box i.e. the main box has to be put by AR in the position marked by yellow border in AR zone.
        \n• Encryption and Decryption keys should be placed in their respective areas.
        \n• Deposition of towers,encryption key and decryption key can be done in any order.
        \n• Deposition of Encryption/decryption keys is not compulsory.But you may do it to increase your points.
        \n\nTASK 3)
        \n• AR will provide the message to MR in the position marked by yellow border in AR zone.
        \n• The message must be placed in the Message Deposition Zone to finish the final task.
        \n• No task will be allowed to performed after the deposition of message.
        \n\nSCORING:
        \nMR:
        \nTASK
        \nPOINTS
        \n\nDeposition of Base of Powerhouse :
        \n15 Points
        \n\nDeposition of Head of Powerhouse :
        \n20 Points
        \n\nDeposition of tower in tower position :
        \n20 Points
        \n\nDeposition of tower switch :
        \n40 Points
        \n\nDeposition of Encryption key :
        \n20 Points
        \n\nDeposition of Decryption key :
        \n50 Points
        \n\nDeposition of the message :
        \n25 Points
        \n\nScore : 15 + 20 + (20*2) + (40*2) + 20 + 50 + 25 = 250 Points
        \nAR:
        \nTASK
        \nPOINTS
        \nDeposition of cubical object to the deposition point :
        \n20 Points
        \nDeposition of cubical object in the area with yellow border :
        \n40 Points
        \nBonus 50 points will be awarded for AR (completing the task) depositing all the boxes to the deposition zones in the first trial
        \nScore : 20*3 + 40 + (50) = 100 + (50) = 150 Points
        \n\nMiscellaneous:
        \n• Points will be awarded only if object is deposited correctly i.e. it is fully within respective zone and not in contact with any part of the robot.
        \n• Objects deposited after the allotted time limit will not be given any points.
        \n• Points will be awarded with clear indication from judges.
        \n\nMatch Result:
        \n• Match will end if a single team completes following tasks:
        \n• MR places the message in the message deposition zone.
        \n• Team completing all the above tasks will be declared winner of the match.
        \n• If both teams fail to complete above tasks in 4.5 minutes, then the match result will be decided on the basis of points scored by the teams.
        \n• Team scoring maximum points will be declared winner of the match in such case.
        \n• In case of clash at the message deposition zone, both the MR will start at their respective start zone.
        \n• In case of Tie, preferences will be as follows
        \n1)No. of Boxes deposited by the AR.
        \n2)No. Of Boxes deposited by the MR.
        \n3)Rematch</string>
    <string name="event_structure_bot_wrestling">Qualifier Round
        \n1. Qualifier round will be held prior to the knockout round. The duration of the qualifying round will be 2 minutes.
        \n2. In each match, two teams will compete against each other at a time and try to earn maximum points.
        \n3. The teams will be ranked according to their points.
        \n4. Top 16 teams will qualify for the finals. Other than this, the performance in the qualifier round is of no significance to the contest.
        \n\nKnockout Round:
        \n1. Two teams will compete against each other like in the qualifier one.
        \n2. Each round will have a duration of 2 minute. The team which wins two rounds first (each of 2 min) will be declared the winner of the match.
        \n3. The team that pushes the opposition robot out of the arena (i.e. out of the red zone) is declared as the winner of that round.
        \n4. The scoring pattern will be uniform throughout and the scores will be considered only in case of a tie i.e. if no team is able to push the opponent’s robot out of the arena in that round.
        \n5. In case of a tie in a round (i.e. none of the team’s robot is able to push the opposition robot out of the arena), the winner will be decided by the points earned by each team in that round.
        \n6. In case of a tie in the match, the winner of the match will be decided by a tie breaker.
        \n\nTASK:
        \n1. Teams must build a robot which can be wirelessly controlled using a remote. Wireless control is compulsory.
        \n2. The aim of the robot is to push the robot of the opposite team out of the arena. The team doing so wins the match.
        \n\nArena:
        \n1. The arena will be square in shape of side 3000 mm.
        \n2. The main arena will be a circular in shape with a maximum diameter 2400 mm.
        \n3. It will consist of two concentric circles of diameter 2000 mm and 2400 mm.
        \n4. The inner circular area is blue in color and is called the “Blue Zone” while the outer circular area is red in color and is called the “Red Zone”.
        \n5. A center white line of 30 mm width divides the arena into two equal halves.
        \n6. There are white squares of 300 mm x 300 mm on the opposite sides of this line that indicate the starting zones of the two competing teams.
        \n7. The arena will be made up of wood and the markings on it including all the zones will be drawn using paint.
        \n\nMachine Specifications:
        \n1. The machine should fit in a square of 300mm x 300mm. There is no height limit.
        \n2. The combined weight of the robot and the remote must not exceed 3 kg.
        \n3. If the team is using a laptop or a mobile phone for controlling the robot then its weight is not included in the above.
        \n4. The robot must be stable and must stand on its own at the beginning of the run when put in the starting point. Robots not fulfilling this criterion will be disqualified.
        \n5. During the match, the robot can expand itself provided it does not damage the arena in anyway. However, the machine should not leave anything behind while competing. The machine should not scratch, damage or destroy the arena or accompanying parts of arena.
        \nThe machine should not shoot anything at the opponent’s robot.
        \n6. Any robot found damaging the arena will be immediately disqualified. The final decision is at the discretion of the organizers.
        \n7. Readymade (market sold) robot with or without modifications will not be allowed in the competition.
        \n\nPower supply:
        \n1. Machine must be completely self-contained and should receive no outside assistance. It should not use an energy source employing a combustion process.
        \n2. Machine should have an on-board power supply. No external power supply is allowed.
        \n3. Voltage on the machine at any point should not exceed 12 V DC.
        \n\nPoints:
        \n1. Each team earns 10 points for pushing the opposition in the red zone and 50 points for pushing the opponent out of the red zone.
        \n2. When a robot is knocked out of the red zone by opponent robot, 20 points will be deducted from the knocked out team.
        \n3. If a robot goes in the red zone on its own without being pushed by the opponent robot then 10 points will be deducted from the teams score entering the red zone. No points will be given to the opponent in such a case.
        \n4. If a robot is not in working state (i.e. no movement is seen) at the start of a round for any reason, 20 points will be deducted from that team.
        \n5. If there is still a tie on the basis of the scores then a rematch of 1 minute will be played by the involved teams until we get a winner.
        \n6. The score of team may be negative.
        \n7. Judges’ decision shall be treated as final and binding to all.
        \n8. The organizers reserve the rights to change any or all of the above rules as they deem fit.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_virtual_robotics">• Contestants will design 3D models based on certain themes of Robotics.
        \n• The Contestants will give a short presentation explaining in brief, their models.
        \n\nROUNDS:
        \nThe competition will have a single round where in all the contestants will present their ideas.
        \n\nThemes:
        \nThe designs that will be presented by the contestants should fall into one of the following four categories:
        \n1. Domestic Robots: They may include robots that make daily household work simpler.
        \n2. Robotic Arms: This category includes innovative designs of robotic arms and/or grippers that can be used for picking up various objects.
        \n3. Industrial Robots: Robots under this category are the ones which are used in industries to make the manufacturing processes automated and more efficient.
        \n4. Military Application Robots: Robots that can be used for surveillance or can move through rough terrains fall into this category.
        \n\nCompetition Rules:
        \n• The 3D model should be created on any of the following software:
        \n1. SOLIDWORKS
        \n2. CATIA
        \n3. CREO
        \n• Simulation of the 3D model is not compulsory but would be preferred.
        \n• The presentation delivered by the participant should be under 20 minutes.
        \n• If contestants have participated as a team, each member should present the idea for a maximum of 10 minutes.
        \n• Contestants should carry their own laptop containing the design as well as a USB drive containing the design files.
        \n\nCriterion for Winner:
        \nThe contestant with the most innovative design in any of the above-mentioned categories will be decided as the winner by the judges.</string>

    <string name="event_structure_the_amazing_race">Round 1 (Elimination Rounds): The elimination rounds will occur on Day 1 and Day 2, first half of the three days of MindSpark’17.
        \n\nRound 2 (Final Round): Second half of Day 2 of MindSpark’17. Duration: The event will begin in the morning and can continue till 6 pm.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_bull_run">Round 1: Simple Question/Answer Round. Serves as the Elimination Round.
        \n\nRound 2: Based on the Indian Market
        \n\nRound 3: Final Round, based on the Indian + International Market
        \nAny other details of the event will be revealed on the spot.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_bidzkreig_1">Round 1: This round will consist of a written test in the form of multiple choice questions. Negative marking will be implemented, details to be disclosed at the time of event. All the questions will be cricket-based.
        \n\nRound 2: Qualified teams will have to form a cricket team consisting of atleast 5 bowlers and a maximum of 2 wicket-keepers. There should be at least 5 Indian players. An all-rounder can be considered as a bowler or batsman. Each team will be permitted to buy a maximum of 15 players. If a player has not been bought by any team, that player will not be available for bid again. This round shall consist of 2 parts.
        \nPart 1: The round will consist auctioning of certain number of marquee players. The bidding process shall be the same as that used for normal players. Each marquee player will have a joker card, which will be awarded to the teams answering a question based on the player correctly. The team holding the joker card will be able to match the maximum bid if they so wish. The joker cards are non-transferable and are to be used only for a particular player.
        \nPart 2: The round will consist of the auction of the remaining players in the roster.
        \nTeams will be able to choose more than 15 players only after all other teams have 15 players in their list.
        \nThe team with maximum cumulative points will be the winner.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="event_structure_bidzkreig_2">ROUND 1:
        \nTeams will be given limited amount of money to pick 5 players in their team which includes 1 keeper, 1 defender, 2 midfielders and 1 forward. The ratings of the players will correspond to their FIFA‘18 ratings. The participants having the most rated team will qualify for Round 2.
        \n\nROUND 2:
        \nQualified participants will have to form a team consisting of 11 players and coach. The participants will have to make the team in two parts. Part 1 consists of the playing eleven and part 2 consists of buying a coach. 80% of points from part 1 and 20% from part 2 of the participants teams will be added to get a final score. Participants with the highest score will be the winner.
        \n\nPART 1:
        \nParticipating teams will start with a budget of $120 million.
        \nParticipating teams can only make a team from the given set of formations:
        \n4-4-2 (4 defenders, 4 midfielders, 2 forward)
        \n4-3-3 (4 defenders, 3 midfielders, 3 forward)
        \n4-5-1 (4 defenders, 5 midfielders, 1 forward)
        \n3-5-2 (3 defenders, 5 midfielders, 2 forward)
        \n5-3-2 (5 defenders, 3 midfielders, 2 forward)
        \nSelecting a goalkeeper is mandatory. At the beginning of the round, there will be a short quiz session related to football. The winner of the quiz will get $5 million as bonus to buy players.
        \n\nPART 2: When exactly half the players would be sold through the auction process, the "winter transfer window" would start for 15 minutes where all the participating teams can negotiate with other players to buy or sell their player/s which they would have bought until then. Further details will be explained on the spot.
        \nThis part will be conducted after the winter transfer window where the rest of the players will be auctioned. The participants’ will have the freedom to place the players in any position of their team. At the end of the two rounds the participants will be asked to submit their teams and final scores will be evaluated.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_lan_slam">Round 1:
        \n6 rounds.
        \nMap: Mirage
        \nSides (Terrorist / Counter-Terrorist): Coin toss. After 3 rounds, teams will be swapped.
        \nThe top eight teams (based on their high scores will qualify to the next round).
        \n\nRound 2: (Eight Teams)
        \n10 rounds.
        \nMap: Cache
        \nSides (Terrorist / Counter-Terrorist): Coin toss. After 5 rounds, teams will be swapped.
        \n\nRound 3: (Four Teams)
        \n10 rounds.
        \nMap: Inferno
        \nSides (Terrorist / Counter-Terrorist): Coin toss. After 5 rounds, teams will be swapped.
        \nFinal Round: (Two Teams)
        \nBest of 3 Maps: 20 rounds each.
        \nMap: De_dust2(Compulsory) , other 2 maps of Finalists’ choice
        \nSides (Terrorist / Counter-Terrorist): Coin toss. After 10 rounds, teams will be swapped in each of the 3 maps.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_flash">CATEGORIES:
        \n\n1. BEST PICTURE- One picture to be submitted per registration which must be MindSpark’17 related. Should depict the theme of MS’17, preparations, workshops or main event days. Can be clicked using mobile/professional camera.
        \n\n2. BEST VIDEO- MS’17 related.
        \n\ta. Participants are supposed to make a video with duration not more than 90 seconds portraying the theme of MS’17, preparations and showing the key highlights of the event in a creative manner. Just like an after-movie.
        \n\tb. Time-lapses, hyper-lapses, compilation is allowed.
        \n\tc. The participants will be allowed to start shooting from the workshop days.
        \n\td. Use of adobe after-effects, premiere pro or any other relevant video editing software is allowed.
        \n\n3. MOBILE PHOTOGRAPHY: (5 ENTRIES PER REGISTRATION) This category is an open photography competition not restricting to the days of the event and to the theme as well. The motive is to encourage any form of mobile photography across all the genres. The entries must be clicked using mobiles only and can be based on any theme.
        \n\n4. PROFESSIONAL CAMERA PHOTOGRAPHY: (5 ENTRIES PER REGISTRATION). This is also an open themed competition with the difference that all entries must’ve been shot using a professional camera (SLRs and Point ‘n Shoot cameras).</string>

    <string name="event_structure_chakravyuh">Round 1: Written elimination round, with no multiple-choice questions. No negative marking.
        \n\nRound 2: Top 6 teams will be selected for the final round, the details of which will be disclosed on the spot.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_indikya">City Round (excluding Pune):
        \n2 sets of pre-made questions will be mailed to Proctors from the respective cities where they will conduct the prelims and finals. The winner from each city will be then invited to Pune for the qualifying round.
        \nPune Round: A written round will be conducted in CoEP during Mindspark’17 where the top 6 teams will be selected for the qualifying round.
        \nQualifying Round: The 6 teams from city rounds and 6 teams from Pune round will be randomly split into 2 groups of 6 teams each. A separate short round will be conducted for both the groups and 3 top teams from both the groups go through to the finals.
        \nFinal Round: Top 6 teams as mentioned above will be selected for the final round, the details of which will be disclosed on the spot.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_torquest">Round 1: Written elimination round, with no multiple-choice questions. No negative marking.
        \n\nRound 2: Top 6 teams will be selected for the final round, the details of which will be disclosed on the spot.</string>

    <string name="event_structure_genius_jr">Preliminary Round: MCQ test based on Mathematics, Science, Logic, Language and General Knowledge. No negative marking.
        \n\nFinal Round: This round will be an online quiz. This quiz will be held at different dates across the states. The score of this round will decide the state champion.
        \nThe online quiz will contain questions of unequal weightage.
        \nThis round will be conducted in COEP campus on the days of MindSpark’17.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_sudoku">Round 1: This will consist of the most basic and easy 9x9 grid sudoku.
        \n\nRound 2: The sudoku in this round will also have the same 9x9 grid, but the puzzle will be more difficult and some of the rules may be tweaked a bit.
        \n\nRound 3: This round will consist of a sudoku puzzle with a change in grid style and rules of solving as well as an increased difficulty level.
        \n\nNote:The selection criteria for each round will be the accuracy and speed in solving the sudoku puzzle.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_googler">Round 1 :- Each Team will be given 10 Questions whose answers they have to search over google within 10 minutes.
        \n\nRound 2 :- Each team will be given 5 questions to be solved within 5 minutes.</string>

    <string name="event_structure_ham">The various topics that will be covered in the workshop include:
        \n1. Basic Principles of Communication
        \n2. Wireless communication overview
        \n3. Introduction to Amateur radio
        \n4. Satellite applications of Amateur radio
        \n5. Antenna Theory and Practical Antenna Construction
        \n6. Antenna simulation software via presentation (4Nec2 software)
        \n7. Recent trends in communication technologies and smart antennas</string>
    <string name="event_structure_tux">Each day, there will be two sessions.
        \nDay 1, Day 2 and Day 3:
        \nSessions will be disclosed soon.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_stareway_to_heaven">The demonstration will be done in batches of people inside the mobile planetarium in the COEP campus.</string>
    <string name="event_structure_cnc_lathe">Curriculum:
        \n1. Theory session: Comparison of CNC and conventional Lathe machine, basic components of CNC e.g. power supply, manufacturers, MCU, drive system, stepping motor, recirculating balls, coordinate system, part programming, control system e.g. open loop and close loop, CNC tools, STD inserts, specific application of CNCe.g. aerospace, automotive components, advantages and disadvantages of CNC.
        \n2. Question Answer Session (Interactive)
        \n3. Programming Session: Special emphasis on ZERO SETTING of the tool tip, brief introduction of the machine dashboard (Control Panel), "\'"G"\'" codes and "\'"M"\'" codes, stock removal in turning and facing, repetitive, peck drilling, peck grooving cycles, threading cycle, encoding programs for product which includes following operations: facing, turning, taper, fillets/chamfer, threading, grooving.
        \n4. Practical Session: Actual implementation of the programmed codes on the CNC lathe machine with hands on experience. Technical explanation regarding cutting speed, feed values, use of coolant will be given during practical session. If time permits, other CNC machines will be theoretically introduced (apart from the lathe).</string>
    <string name="event_structure_virtual_labs">EVENT DESCRIPTION:
        \nPhysical distance and lack of resources deprives us from performing experiments, especially when they involve sophisticated instruments. Also, good teachers are mostly a scarce resource.
        \n\nThe Virtual Labs 2017 workshop would use the following two approaches:
        \n1. Remotely triggering an experiment in an actual lab.
        \n2. Performing laboratory simulations online.
        \n\nABOUT VIRTUAL LABS:
        \n1. To provide remote-access to labs in various aspects of Science and Engineering.
        \n2. To provide a complete Learning Management System around the Virtual Labs where the students can avail the various tools for learning, including additional web-resources, video-lectures, animated demonstrations and self-evaluation.
        \n3. To share costly equipment and resources, which are otherwise available to limited number of user’s due to time constraints and geographical distance.
        \n\nEVENT STRUCTURE:
        \nSection 1:
        \nAn informative session of lectures on Virtual Labs by esteemed educationists.
        \nSection 2:
        \nA hands-on Virtual Labs tutorial, wherein participants can actually perform the experiments on sophisticated hi- tech lab equipment.</string>


    <string name="event_rules_epitome">1. All team members must come with valid college ID cards and registration receipt.
        \n\n2. The team need to construct the model from provided material only. No extra material will be provided. The team should use only that material which is provided by the organizers. If the material used is other than that provided, then the team will be disqualified immediately.
        \n\n3. Using materials of other participants is also strictly prohibited i.e. using some extra materials.
        \n\n4. One team can make only one model for proposed competition.
        \n\n5. Testing of models will be done according to the serial number given to the teams at the time of commencement of the event. Hence, no team should request for their model to be tested first.
        \n\n6. The decision of the judges and the organizers will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n7. Team members may be from different colleges. However, same person cannot be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n8. All teams must maintain decorum at all times. Organizers may disqualify any team that behaves inappropriately.
        \n\n9. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are, therefore, requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string><string name="event_rules_conquest">1. Use of admixtures and fibers is allowed (maximum up to 3% by weight of cement), however, any other type of reinforcement is not allowed.
        \n\n2. The fibers should be discontinuous and randomly distributed.
        \n\n3. Mention all the details very clearly about fibers, admixtures which are used.
        \n\n4. Prepare a mix design sheet showing details of every constituent of concrete used, i.e. cement, aggregate, and water etc., using Indian Standard (IS) method of mix design.
        \n\n5. Mix design sheet must be signed by Head of your Department with their stamp.
        \n\n6. Special recognition will be given for following the "\'"MindSpark "’"17 Theme Towards Techno-Utopia"\'".
        \n\n7. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) for updates.
        \n\n8. In case of disputes, the decisions of the Event Heads and the Judges will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n9. Teams are expected to maintain decorum at all times. The organizers reserve the right to disqualify any team found behaving inappropriately.
        \n\n10. All team members must carry their college ID cards and registrations receipts.
        \n\n11. Participants must engrave the date of casting clearly on the top of the cylinder. This shall be an additional point in Examination of the cylinder.
        \n\n12. One person may not be a part of multiple teams for this event.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_metropolis">1. Sheets and report must be submitted by 22ndSeptember till 1pm; late entries will not be accepted.
        \n\n2. Teams must construct the model within the given time limit only. No extra time will be given.
        \n\n3. All teams and their respective members should reach the event place in time. Tardiness may be considered as grounds for disqualification.
        \n\n4. All teams must maintain decorum at all times. Organizers may disqualify any team that behaves inappropriately
        \n\n5. Students must bring their valid college identity cards while coming to event.
        \n\n6. Team members may be from different colleges. However, one person cannot be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n7. Basic material will be provided by MindSpark’17 for model making and list of material available will be provided.
        \n\n8. On-spot entries will be accepted for first round only.
        \n\n9. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the website regularly for updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_id_civil">RULES:
        \n\n1. It is mandatory to stick to the problem statement given at the time of rounds.
        \n\n2. The version of AutoCAD used will either be AutoCAD 07 or AutoCAD 10. If the participant wants to use a version other than the ones mentioned above, they must bring their own laptops.
        \n\n3. Creativity, aesthetics and more importantly inculcating the theme ‘Towards Techno-Utopia’ will be considered a crucial point while judging.
        \n\n4. The team members need not be from the same institution.However, a participant cannot be a part of more than one team for the same event.
        \n\n5. In case of disputes, decisions of judges and organizers will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n6. Teams are expected to maintain decorum. The organizers reserve the right to disqualify any team found behaving inappropriately.
        \n\n7. It is mandatory to bring registration receipt and valid college ID. Participants without these may not be allowed to participate in the event.
        \n\n8. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the website (www.mind-spark.org) and their registered email ID regularly for updates.</string><string name="event_rules_assemblix">1. Only participants with a valid college ID card and registration receipt allowed.
        \n\n2. Only UG students and diploma students can participate; No workers/ employees will be allowed to participate.
        \n\n3. There is no restriction of branch. Student from any branch can participate.
        \n\n4. Two students from different colleges can be a part of the same team. However, one person cannot be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n5. Decision taken by the judges and organizers will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n6. All the required tools will be provided at the event venue by the organizers.
        \n\n7. Participants will not be allowed to use mobile phones or any other electronic gadget during the event, except calculators.
        \n\n8. Rules may be changed without any prior intimidation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.
        \n\n9. Participants need to be present at the event venue at least 10 minutes prior to the commencement of the event.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_id_2d">1. Any student with a valid college ID card and registration receipt can participate in the event.
        \n\n2. Students from any branch and any college can form a team. However, no person can be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n3. Decision taken by judges and organizers will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n4. Participants will not be allowed to use mobiles, tabs or any other electronic devices.
        \n\n5. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org), regularly for updates.</string><string name="event_rules_id_3d">1. The decision of the judges and event heads shall be considered final and binding to all. Any participants found misbehaving will be immediately disqualified.
        \n\n2. Only UG students can participate. Workers/employees will not be allowed.
        \n\n3.In case of a tie in the second round, the marks of first round will be considered as the criteria for the selection to the third round.
        \n\n4.In case of tie in the third round, marks of the first and second rounds will be considered as the criteria for deciding the winners. Innovation, sophistication in design and ease of assembly and disassembly will be considered as the criteria for evaluation.
        \n\n5. Participants should be present 30 minutes prior to the commencement of event. Late teams may be disqualified.
        \n\n6. Participants must bring a valid college ID and the registration receipt with them on the day of the event.
        \n\n7. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string><string name="event_rules_mechtrix">1. No external equipment other than that provided by the organizers can be used.
        \n\n2. Using equipment of other participants is also strictly prohibited (i.e. using some extra material).
        \n\n3. The registered teams will have to carry their registration receipt and college ID cards at the time of the event.
        \n\n4. Participants can be of different colleges/institutions. But, one person may not be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n5. The teams must adhere to the spirit of healthy competition and maintain decorum at all times.
        \n\n6. Organizers reserve the right to disqualify any team indulging in misbehavior or violating any rules.
        \n\n7. In case of disputes, the decision of the organizers and the judges will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n8. Any team that is not ready at the specified time will be disqualified from the competition automatically.
        \n\n9. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_turnament">1. If any damage to LATHE M/C, surroundings etc., or any malpractices including negligence during machining will lead to disqualification.
        \n\n2. Fine will be TAKEN if any MAJOR damages to Tool, Lathe Machine or Surroundings occur during Operation.
        \n\n3. After the completion of the task all the accessories must be returned.
        \n\n4. No extra work piece will be provided and carrying of any extra material is banned.
        \n\n5. The judges’ and organizers’ decision will be final, binding to all and irrevocable.
        \n\n6. Participants are responsible for their own safety.
        \n\n7. They should COMPULSORILY have apron and shoes.
        \n\n8. The winner will be decided based on the accuracy, Surface finish and time duration.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_code_junkie">1. Participant can choose from either Ubuntu 12.04 OS with gedit/vim/emacs as text editor and gcc as compiler OR Windows 7 with Turbo C / Dev C++.
        \n\n2. Participants should be First Year or Second Year Undergraduate students.
        \n\n3. Participants need to bring their College ID cards and the receipt of registration during reporting.
        \n\n4. Time slots will be given and participants are expected to follow it strictly.
        \n\n5. Participants are expected to give their correct contact details to get results.
        \n\n6. Further details of the round will be disclosed at the time of event.
        \n\n7. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates. 8. In case of any disputes, the decision of the organizers and the judges will be final and binding to all. 9. Team members may be from different colleges/institutions but one participant may not be a part of multiple teams for the same event.</string><string name="event_rules_code_junkie_pp">1. For rounds 2 and 3, the environment – programming language, IDE, editor, compiler, interpreter, etc. - will be anything you are comfortable with. But please note that:
        \n\ti. OS will be GNU/Linux or Windows.
        \n\tii. In round 2, some questions will be specifically related to C++, Java and Python.
        \n\t(You will be given an option to solve questions either of C++ or Java or Python)
        \n\tiii. For round 3, judging criteria will stress on program efficiency in terms of both time and space. Choose your programming language in this round wisely.
        \n\n2. This event is open to all undergraduate students.
        \n\n3. Participants need to bring their College ID cards and the receipt of registration at the time of reporting.
        \n\n4. Participants are expected to give their correct contact details. (Email ID and phone number).
        \n\n5. Participants are expected to follow the time slots given to them strictly.
        \n\n6. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly.</string><string name="event_rules_xterminate">1. The environment will be either: an Ubuntu 12.04 or higher version OS with emacs/ vim/gedit as text editor and gcc as compiler OR Windows 7 with Turbo C (as per the team’s choice).
        \n\n2. Participants must bring their valid College ID cards and the receipt of registration during reporting. Otherwise, the participant may be disqualified.
        \n\n3. Time slots will be allotted and participants are expected to follow them strictly.
        \n\n4. Participants are expected to give their contact details correctly, so as to inform them about the event and event results.
        \n\n5. Decision of the event heads and the judges shall be considered final and binding to all.
        \n\n6. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are, therefore, requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string><string name="event_rules_retracer">1. Teams are expected to maintain decorum. MindSpark’17 team reserves the right to disqualify any team found misbehaving.
        \n\n2. In case of any disputes, the decision of event heads and judges will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n3. Rules of the event may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.
        \n\n4. Participants must carry their school ID card and the registration receipt.
        \n\n5. Participants must be present on time at the given venue. Late entries will not be entertained.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_predict_x">1. Predict-X is an online event that will be conducted for 30 days.
        \n\n2. There is no restriction on its participation and the participants can participate from anywhere across the world.
        \n\n3. There is no restriction of branch. Student from any branch can participate.
        \n\n4. Two students from different colleges can be a part of the same team. However, one person cannot be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n5. Decision taken by the judges and organizers will be binding to all and will be considered final and binding to all.
        \n\n6. Teams who do not register will not be eligible for prizes and their solution will not be taken under consideration.
        \n\n7. Participants will access their datasets and submit their solutions by using either their Facebook or Gmail accounts on Hacker Rank.
        \n\n8. Teams who cannot register offline, may register online on the website of MindSpark’17 (www.mind-spark.org)
        \n\n9. Rules may be changed without any prior intimidation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string>\n<string name="event_rules_hackathon2.0">1. Teams will be given 2-3 problem statements to choose from and develop solution in the 24-hour time period. The solution may consist of a web app, mobile app, data visualization, design prototype, or a business plan.
        \n\n2. Participants should develop an application of their choice to best fit the solution of the given problem statement. Mentors will be present at the location to help the teams and to check on what the teams are developing for some period of the Hackathon.
        \n\n3. Every team will have to explain their product individually to our mentors roaming around and will have to give a final presentation to our judging panel, out of which the winner will be chosen.
        \n\n4. Every team should bring their own electronics appliances they may require, e.g. Laptops, Mouse, Pen drives, etc. The use of different types of hardware and software is encouraged throughout the event. A checklist will be sent to the participants a few weeks before the event.
        \n\n5. Participants must bring their registration receipts, college ID and various things which would be mentioned in the checklist, while coming to event.
        \n\n6. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.
        \n\n7. In case of any disputes, the decision of the organizers and the judges will be final and binding to all.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_circuit_fixer_1">1. Only students from first year and second year are allowed to participate.
        \n\n2. All the participants should have valid ID card of their respective institute with them along with the registration receipt.
        \n\n3. The hardware necessary for the final round will be provided by the organizers.
        \n\n4. The decision of judges and the organizers will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n5. In case any assistance is needed during the event, the teams should approach only the event coordinators/organizers.
        \n\n6. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) for updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_circuit_fixer_2">1. The event is open to all undergraduate students.
        \n\n2. All the participants should have valid ID card of their respective institute with them along with the registration receipt.
        \n\n3. The hardware necessary for the finals will be provided by the organizers.
        \n\n4. The decision of judges will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n5. In case any assistance is needed during the event, the teams should only approach the organizers.
        \n\n6. Participants are expected to be present at the given venue on time.
        \n\n7. Pin diagrams for Round 3 will be provided.
        \n\n8. Marking Scheme will be decided on the spot.
        \n\n9. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_encrypto">1. Participants must carry their original college ID and registration receipt at the time of event. Entry will be denied if a participant is without either of these two.
        \n\n2. On the spot registrations are also allowed.
        \n\n3. Any form of cheating/use of unfair means will NOT be tolerated and the concerned teams will be disqualified immediately.
        \n\n4. The decision of Judges and Event Heads will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n5. Non-programmable calculators are allowed.
        \n\n6. Team members may be from same or different colleges/institutes. However, one person cannot be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n7. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check MindSpark’16 rules on website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_microapps">1. The event is open for undergraduate students only.
        \n\n2. Participants are required to give correct contact details, so as to inform them about the event updates.
        \n\n3. Participants must bring their College ID cards and receipt of registration during reporting.
        \n\n4. Only "\'"C"\'" language can be used. The IDE to be used is CCS (which will be introduced prior to the round in which it is required).
        \n\n5. The microcontroller and other hardware will be provided by the organizers.
        \n\n6. The decision of the judges and the organizers will be final.
        \n\n7. The organizers have the right to change the above-mentioned rules without giving any prior notice (participants are requested to check the website for updates: www.mind-spark.org.).
        \n\n8. Registration at the first day of the event will be there but preference will be given to pre-registered teams.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_on_the_etch">1. Display of Microphotograph (captured on Optical microscope/SEM/TEM) during presentation is mandatory. Participants failing to produce the microphotograph may be disqualified.
        \n\n2. Fake micrographs will lead to the disqualification of the team.
        \n\n3. The sample must strictly be prepared by the participants.
        \n\n4. The sample selected for microstructural observation should be mounted by either hot or cold mounting method. Both, cross section (Radial in case of a cylindrical specimen) and longitudinal section of the same sample must be mounted together. Only longitudinal section of the sample will be accepted only if the sample has very thin diameter i.e. less than 5 mm.
        \n\n5. The microphotograph captured on either Optical Microscope OR Scanning Electron Microscope(SEM) OR Transmission Electron microscope(TEM) is expected to be presented with following mandatory specifications:
        \ni) The magnification or scale must be burnt into the micrograph.
        \nii) The size of the printed microphotograph must be 200mm*250 mm or A4 size.
        \niii) The composition of the sample is to be presented along with the micrograph. If participants are unable to know the composition of their specimen sampled from an unknown component, they can refer the available research papers and literature regarding the component. If still they are unable to solve the problem, they are free to contact the event heads.
        \niv) The typical features (advantages, disadvantages etc.) of the concerned microstructure.
        \nv) Typical applications of the components having the concerned microstructure in industry.
        \nvi) A 1 or 2- page hand-out comprising of summary of the specimen preparation to introduce it to judges in least possible words.
        \nvii) The mount should comprise of the sample whose micrograph is captured.
        \n\n6. Participants are expected to prepare a sample of any failed industrial component or any other metallic spare part which is readily available and free of cost. The metal objects which are generally used by us in day-to-day life will also be accepted. Ferrous alloys will be preferred for sampling. This change has specifically been made in the competition to develop practical approach towards sampling of specimens.
        \n\n7. To give more clarification regarding the points ‘5.iii’ and ‘5.iv’, a small session will be conducted few days prior to the event which will help participants to apply the theoretical concepts about different microstructures in revealing the microstructures of the components used in practice. Date, timings and more details about the session will be informed afterwards to the registered participants.
        \n\n8. Micrographs are not allowed to be captured on the day of the event.
        \n\n9. Presentation of photographs on laptops is not allowed. Only printed micrographs are allowed to be presented before the Judges.
        \n\n10. Participants should carry their college ID cards as a proof for identity on the day of the event along with the receipt of registration.
        \n\n11. Decision made by the judges and organizers will be final and binding to all the participant teams in case of any tie.
        \n\n12. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are expected to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) for the updates. In case of any small query or doubt, feel free to ask the event heads.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_dexters_lab">1. Participants from same or different institutions may be a part of the same team. However, no participant must be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n2. Participants must carry a valid college ID and the receipt of registration. Without the mentioned documents, teams will not be allowed to participate in the event.
        \n\n3. Decision made by the judges and event heads will be final and binding for all the participant teams.
        \n\n4. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string><string name="event_rules_wheelomation">1.Each team can comprise of a minimum of two members and a maximum of five members.
        \n\n2.Each member must be a student with a valid ID card. All teams must be present on specified date for inspection, along with their registration receipt. This is to ensure that the machine has been made according to the given specifications.
        \n\n3.The eligible teams will be given their practice slots. During this time, the teams can practice on the track; however, this permission is given on a first come first serve basis. So, it is advisable to secure your slot well before time.
        \n\n4.Participants must use remote with frequency of band spectrum 2.4 GHz only. No power supply will be given on the track.
        \n\n5. Team members are not permitted to touch either their machines or those of their opponents once the race begins (unless there is a need to lift the machine). The penalty for doing so on invalid grounds is disqualification.
        \n\n6. Teams are prohibited from purposefully damaging the machine of the opponent team. If found guilty, the concerned team will be disqualified.
        \n\n7. If the machine is found unsafe to run on the track, that team will be disqualified from the race. The organizers’ decision will be final and binding to all in this respect. No damage to the track will be tolerated and if found guilty, the responsible team will be disqualified.
        \n\n8. The vehicles are not allowed to leave any loose parts or any extra part on any part of the arena.
        \n\n9. Any vehicle disintegrating during the race will be disqualified. The vehicle must remain intact throughout the race. Once the race gets started, the participants must complete the race.
        \n\n10. The track will have checkpoints at regular intervals. If the machine halts, tumbles or goes off the arena at any point, one of the team members is allowed to lift it up and place it at the nearest completed checkpoint. However, the timer will still be running, in the meantime.
        \n\n11. Persons from different institutes can be a part of the same team. However, one person cannot be a part of multiple teams for the same event. Only undergraduate students may participate.
        \n\n12. The judges"\'" and organizers"\'" decisions shall be treated as final and binding to all. The organizers reserve the rights to change any/or all of the above rules as they deem fit.
        \n\n13. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are, therefore, requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.
        \n\nARENA Details:
        \n1. The race track will be a combination of on road and off-road tracks with many hurdles.
        \n2. Participants are advised to use proper suspension and tires to endure the bumps.
        \n3. Check points will be provided on track where the machine can restart, in case of a disturbance.
        \n4. Details about track will be uploaded on MindSpark’17 website.
        \n\nSpecifications:
        \n\n1. ENGINE:
        \nMaximum piston displacement allowed is 4 cc. The car should be powered by only one IC engine. Any machine which uses DC Motors for propulsion will be disqualified. However, DC motors and servos can be used for steering mechanisms or any other control mechanisms, apart from propulsion.
        \n\n2. FUEL:
        \nThe percentage of nitromethane should not exceed 20% by volume in the fuel. Readymade fuel can be used.
        \n\n3. VEHICLE DIMENSIONS:
        \nMachine should fit in a box of dimensions
        \n650 mm x 500 mm x 400 mm (lxbxh) at any time during the race. The external device which is used to control the machine is not included in the size constraint. Antennae are exempt from the height restriction.
        \n\n4. PARTS THAT ARE TO BE FABRICATED BY THE PARTICIPANTS: The chassis, Suspensions system, Steering mechanism and Brakes.
        \n\n5. The machine must not be made from Lego parts, or any ready-made assembly kits other than the parts mentioned above. Readily available chassis layouts are not allowed. Any machine found having a ready-made chassis will be disqualified.
        \n\n6. Parts that can be directly procured from the market:
        \nGear box assembly, Differentials (if used)
        \nSuspension springs, Shock absorbers
        \nTires and wheels (You are advised to use tires of good width for better performance on dirt tracks).
        \nClutch System, Brake System, Engine, Carburetor, Servo Motors, Wheel hub.
        \n\n7. POWER SUPPLY:
        \nThe machine must have an on-board power supply to provide power to any mechanism requiring electric power not exceeding 12 V.
        \n\n8. RADIO CONTROLLERS:
        \nThe machine must be necessarily controlled by a wireless remote-control system. Note: You may use clutch mechanism between the engine and the wheel, cooling mechanism to prevent overheating of the engine and air filters as dirt might cause serious problems to the engine for better performance.
        \n\n9. STEERING MECHANISM:
        \nThe entire steering mechanism must be fabricated by the participants i.e. any part connected to the steering part rigidly must be fabricated by the participants; failing to do so the team will be disqualified. However, the heim joint, knuckle arm, studs and wheel hub can be ready-made.
        \n\n10. SUSPENSION MECHANISM:
        \nThe suspension mechanism must be fabricated by the participants except the shock absorbers. The suspension tower and the suspension arms must be fabricated by the participants.
        \n\n11. BRAKES:
        \nThe brake mechanism must be disc brakes only. The disc pads used must be made by participants.
        \n\n12. Participants having doubts regarding specifications should email their queries to wheelomation@mind-spark.org and are requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly, for further updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_the_wright_turn_glider">1. Participants that will use ready-made parts (wings, rudder, etc.) will be disqualified.
        \n\n2. Gliders’ will be judged on the basis of time of flight, Range, Aerodynamic stability during flight, etc.
        \n\n3. As soon as the glider touches the ground no further distance covered by it will be considered.
        \n\n4. Based on MS-17’s theme (Towards Techno-Utopia) Gliders that have a modern design will be given bonus points. (eg: Morphing Wings)
        \n\n5. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are, therefore, requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_the_wright_turn_rc_plane">1. Participants must design and build their own aircraft. Use of ready-to- fly (RTF) kits and almost ready-to- fly kits are strictly not allowed.
        \n\n2. Only electric powered RC planes are allowed. Use of IC Engine is strictly prohibited. Electric Motor of maximum 200gms is permitted.
        \n\n3. Participants are free to use any material of their choice. Participants are advised to take special safety precautions for their aircraft. Organizers will not be responsible for any damage caused to the model or its electrical components during the event.
        \n\n4. Participants must be present at the event site before or at the reporting time. Teams arriving late will be disqualified.
        \n\n5. To avoid interference, all teams must hand over their transmitters to organizing team before the event.
        \n\n6. An aircraft is defined as a vehicle which experiences exactly 4 forces – lift, drag, thrust and weight at any time during its flight.
        \n\n7. The event is open to all people who are not 26 years of age or older at the time of the event.
        \n\n8. Students and others will be placed in separate groups and marked accordingly.
        \n\n9. Maximum 5 participants are allowed in each team. Team members can be from same or different institutes.
        \n\n10. However, one participant may not be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n11. Judges’ and organizers’ decision on any matter will be final and binding to all.
        \nAIRCRAFT SPECIFICATIONS:
        \n\n1. Maximum wingspan – 40 inches
        \n\n2. Maximum motor power- 1.5KW
        \n\n3. The voltage of the battery used should not be more than 12V.
        \n\n4. It is recommendable to include a good landing gear system in the design and construction phase of your aircraft. Remember, taking-off and landing are very important phases of this competition. If anyone wants HAND LAUNCH, points for take-off will be deducted.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_aqualympics">1. Students from different institutes can be part of the same team. However, one person cannot be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n2. Students should build their own boat. Outsourcing (using readymade kits or mechanisms) is not allowed. Violation of this rule will lead to disqualification.
        \n\n3. The boat’s shaft must touch the surface of the water i.e. air boats are not allowed.
        \n\n4. The exterior part of the boat shouldn’t be sharp and pointed which might cause damage to the arena. Any boat found damaging the arena would be disqualified.
        \n\n5. Use of IC (Internal Combustion) engine is not allowed.
        \n\n6. External Motors, batteries and remote controls are allowed. There is no restriction on number of D.C. motors used.
        \n\n7. Only onboard power supply is allowed. Battery Voltage should not exceed 12 volts.
        \n\n8. All the teams will have to submit their remotes before the start of the competition. These remotes will be handed back to the team before their turn.
        \n\n9. Laptop/personal computers are not allowed near arena. Devices using Bluetooth are not allowed.
        \n\n10. The organizers are not responsible for any kind of damage to the boat once it enters the arena.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_contraption">1. The minimum and maximum time for contraption is 2 minutes and 10 minutes respectively. After 10 minutes, 30 points per minute will be deducted from the total score.
        \n\n2. In the first trial, 3 hand touches are allowed without deduction of points. Before the fourth-hand touch one would be given choice to go for fourth hand touch or to go for second trial. For 4th, 5th and 6th 30, 60 and 120 points will be deducted respectively from the total score.
        \n\n3. In case of second trial, 2 hand touches will be allowed with deduction of 50 and 80 points for each. Further average of two trials will be considered. The team will be disqualified if they exceed permissible number of hand touches in the respective trail.
        \n\n4. A set-up time of 3 hours and 1 hour will be given for each team for first trial and second trial of the model respectively. Only 2 trials are allowed.
        \n\n5. Final decision made by judges and organizers will be binding to all.
        \n\n6. Each team should perform the 2 tasks as mentioned in the problem statement in the same sequence.
        \n\n7. No alteration in any step will be allowed during the trial of the contraption.
        \n\n8. A space of 2m*2m*3m (l*b*h) will be provided to each team.
        \n\n9. Students should carry proof of identity issued by their institution.
        \n\n10. Each team can have a maximum of 4 members.
        \n\n11. Same person cannot be a member of more than one team. All teams involving common person as a participant will be disqualified. Participants are required to report at 7.30 a.m.
        \n\n12. Participants should take due safety measures in their models.
        \n\n13. Rules are subject to without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.
        \n\n14. All decisions of Judges, Event Heads and Organizers will be final and binding to all participants. No arguments shall be entertained.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_byldan">1. The most creative team presenting the brightest ideas wins.
        \n\n2. The teams will be given a set amount of time for submission in first round failing which they will be disqualified.
        \n\n3. Implementation of external ideas is allowed as long as source is mentioned.
        \n\n4. All team members must come with valid college ID cards and registration receipt.
        \n\n5. Presentation of designs will be done according to the serial number given to the particular team at the time of commencement of the event. Hence, no team should request for their design to be presented first.
        \n\n6. The decision of the judges and the organizers will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n7. Team members may be from different colleges. However, same person cannot be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n8. All teams must maintain decorum at all times. Organizers may disqualify any team that behaves inappropriately.
        \n\n9. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are, therefore, requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string><string name="event_rules_ppt_comp_it">1. Standard Paper format: Paper must be in any STANDARD format. Paper should be essentially in a two-column format and should not exceed 15 pages. Paper should be in Times New Roman font of size 12. For headings, you can use bold and a font of size 16. Paper must contain index, abstract, introduction, point wise description of subject and conclusion and references at the end. Paper must be preceded by a cover page specifying the title of the paper, names of authors, their college names and their contact numbers and email ids.
        \n\n2. All papers should have a bibliography/works-cited page and appropriate footnotes.
        \n\n3. Papers omitting a bibliography or using plagiarized material will be automatically disqualified.
        \n\n4. Paper submitted should be strictly in PDF Format.
        \n\n5. For further details - an example paper in IEEE format and the cover page of the paper, please refer our website (www.mind-spark.org)
        \n\n6. Abstract should not exceed 1 page and Paper should not exceed 15 pages. The subject of the mail with the attached abstract and later, the final paper should be the discipline under which the paper is categorized.
        \n\n7. The mail should contain:
        \ni. Title- theme of the paper.
        \nii. Name of both the authors.
        \niii. Phone no of both the authors.
        \niv. Email ID.
        \n\n8.Participants should submit the papers with in the due time. (before last day of submission, no late submissions will be entertained)
        \n\n9.Teams selected for round two will be contacted personally.
        \n\n10. Bring your college I-Card and registration receipt on event day. All teams and their respective members should reach the event place in time.
        \n\n11. Please bring your power point presentation in a pen drive and mail the power point presentation on your own Email ID. Please bring 2 hard copies of the submitted paper on the day of the event. Paper and Power Point Presentation should be in 2010-2013 format.
        \n\n12. The teams will get 10+2 minutes for presentation followed by a Q and A session.
        \n\n13. Persons from different institutions can be a part of the same team. However, one person may not be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n14. Judges and organizers reserve the right to modify the rules without prior intimation.
        \n\n15. Participants are required to check the updates for the same on the official MindSpark\'17 website. ( www.mind-spark.org). Participants can choose any number of topics and present their paper on the relevant topic.
        \n\n16. Participants can present multiple papers, based on number of registrations they have done. Innovativeness of the topic under a theme will be given credit.
        \n\n17. Original contribution to the paper will be highly encouraged. Only pure technical papers would be considered for short listing.
        \n\n18. Use your discretion to judge whether your topic fits into the chosen theme.
        \n\n19. The list of topics will be made available on site.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_ppt_mech_prod_meta">I. REGISTRATION
        \n\nRegistration must be done along with the submission of abstract. Nobody is exempted from the registration fees. Multiple entries are allowed, however there shall be no concession offered for the second entry.
        \n\nParticipants are requested to include their valid email address and contact number while registering for the event.
        \n\nII. ABSTRACT AND PAPER
        \n\n1. Format: The title should be written in Bold and in font size-20. Authors’ name, affiliation and subsections in paper must be of font size-14. The text must be of font size-12. Subsection titles must be bold and capital numbered in Roman Characters. The abstract should not exceed 700 words and the total paper length should not exceed four pages (including references).
        \n*The font type ‘TIMES NEW ROMAN’ shall be used for the entire paper*
        \n\n2. Submission: Researchers must submit their abstracts and full texts before the deadline. Abstracts submitted beyond the deadline will not be accepted. Students must submit their abstracts and papers in the PDF, however the original text may be written in Microsoft Word or LaTeX.
        \nResearchers shall send their abstracts and texts to ppt_mechprodmeta@mind-spark.org
        \n\n3. Ethics: Papers must contain relevant and necessary bibliography. Work without references will be disqualified. Participants are required to submit a scanned copy of their valid college ID along with the abstract. The same, along with registration receipt, shall be produced at the time of the final round.
        \n\n4. Research: Research work carried out in 2017 only will be accepted. The work, if already published in a journal/ conference, will not be accepted. The topics of research could be inter-disciplinary (please refer to FAQs for encouraged research areas)
        \n\nIII. SELECTION AND PRESENTATION
        \n\nThe decision of the review committee shall be final regarding the acceptance of submitted titles. Collaborative research is permitted provided the collaborators are students enrolled in the college in question. Fifteen minutes will be given for presentation in the final round. The presentation in the final round could be in .ppt(x) or .pdf (if prepared in LaTeX/ Overleaf).
        \n*The language of communication must be English*.
        \n\nDEADLINES:
        \n\nAbstract submission: 25th August 2017
        \n\nFull Text Submission: 7th September
        \n\nFinal Full Text submission: 14th September</string>
    <string name="event_rules_ppt_eei">1. Standard Paper format: Paper must be in any STANDARD format. Paper should be essentially in a two-column format and should not exceed 15 pages. Paper should be in Times New Roman font of size 12. For headings, you can use bold and a font of size 16. Paper must contain index, abstract, introduction, point wise description of subject and conclusion and references at the end. Paper must be preceded by a cover page specifying the title of the paper, names of authors, their college names and their contact numbers and email ids.
        \n\n2. All papers should have a bibliography/works-cited page and appropriate footnotes.
        \n\n3. Papers omitting a bibliography or using plagiarized material will be automatically disqualified.
        \n\n4. Paper submitted should be strictly in PDF Format.
        \n\n5. For further details - an example paper in IEEE format and the cover page of the paper, please refer our website (www.mind-spark.org)
        \n\n6. Abstract should not exceed 1 page and Paper should not exceed 15 pages. The subject of the mail with the attached abstract and later, the final paper should be the discipline under which the paper is categorized.
        \n\n7. The mail should contain:
        \ni. Title- theme of the paper.
        \nii. Name of both the authors.
        \niii. Phone no of both the authors.
        \niv. Email ID.
        \n\n8.Participants should submit the papers with in the due time. (before last day of submission, no late submissions will be entertained)
        \n\n9.Teams selected for round two will be contacted personally.
        \n\n10. Bring your college I-Card and registration receipt on event day. All teams and their respective members should reach the event place in time.
        \n\n11. Please bring your power point presentation in a pen drive and mail the power point presentation on your own Email ID. Please bring 2 hard copies of the submitted paper on the day of the event. Paper and Power Point Presentation should be in 2010-2013 format.
        \n\n12. The teams will get 10+2 minutes for presentation followed by a Q and A session.
        \n\n13. Persons from different institutions can be a part of the same team. However, one person may not be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n14. Judges and organizers reserve the right to modify the rules without prior intimation.
        \n\n15. Participants are required to check the updates for the same on the official MindSpark\'17 website. ( www.mind-spark.org). Participants can choose any number of topics and present their paper on the relevant topic.
        \n\n16. Participants can present multiple papers, based on number of registrations they have done. Innovativeness of the topic under a theme will be given credit.
        \n\n17. Original contribution to the paper will be highly encouraged. Only pure technical papers would be considered for short listing.
        \n\n18. Use your discretion to judge whether your topic fits into the chosen theme.
        \n\n19. The list of topics will be made available on site.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_ppt_civil">1. Standard Paper format: Paper must be in any STANDARD format. Paper should be essentially in a two-column format and should not exceed 15 pages. Paper should be in Times New Roman font of size 12. For headings, you can use bold and a font of size 16. Paper must contain index, abstract, introduction, point wise description of subject and conclusion and references at the end. Paper must be preceded by a cover page specifying the title of the paper, names of authors, their college names and their contact numbers and email ids.
        \n\n2. All papers should have a bibliography/works-cited page and appropriate footnotes.
        \n\n3. Papers omitting a bibliography or using plagiarized material will be automatically disqualified.
        \n\n4. Paper submitted should be strictly in PDF Format.
        \n\n5. For further details - an example paper in IEEE format and the cover page of the paper, please refer our website (www.mind-spark.org)
        \n\n6. Abstract should not exceed 1 page and Paper should not exceed 15 pages. The subject of the mail with the attached abstract and later, the final paper should be the discipline under which the paper is categorized.
        \n\n7. The mail should contain:
        \ni. Title- theme of the paper.
        \nii. Name of both the authors.
        \niii. Phone no of both the authors.
        \niv. Email ID.
        \n\n8.Participants should submit the papers with in the due time. (before last day of submission, no late submissions will be entertained)
        \n\n9.Teams selected for round two will be contacted personally.
        \n\n10. Bring your college I-Card and registration receipt on event day. All teams and their respective members should reach the event place in time.
        \n\n11. Please bring your power point presentation in a pen drive and mail the power point presentation on your own Email ID. Please bring 2 hard copies of the submitted paper on the day of the event. Paper and Power Point Presentation should be in 2010-2013 format.
        \n\n12. The teams will get 10+2 minutes for presentation followed by a Q and A session.
        \n\n13. Persons from different institutions can be a part of the same team. However, one person may not be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n14. Judges and organizers reserve the right to modify the rules without prior intimation.
        \n\n15. Participants are required to check the updates for the same on the official MindSpark\'17 website. ( www.mind-spark.org). Participants can choose any number of topics and present their paper on the relevant topic.
        \n\n16. Participants can present multiple papers, based on number of registrations they have done. Innovativeness of the topic under a theme will be given credit.
        \n\n17. Original contribution to the paper will be highly encouraged. Only pure technical papers would be considered for short listing.
        \n\n18. Use your discretion to judge whether your topic fits into the chosen theme.
        \n\n19. The list of topics will be made available on site.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_search_n_destroy">Competition:
        \n\n1. Each contesting team will be given 2 minutes as dry run on arena before the match.
        \n\n2. In dry run, team can calibrate sensors and can explore the entire arena.
        \n\n3. After dry run, programming of robot is not allowed.
        \n\n4. The starting procedure of the bot should be simple and should not involve giving the bot any manual force or impulse in any direction.
        \n\n5. Duration of match is 4 minutes.
        \n\n6. Once match is started only one member of each team i.e. the operator will be allowed to enter the arena after permission from organizers.
        \n\n7. The match shall start from the start box. The machine will start in only one direction as specified by the organizers. It cannot start in either direction. The operator may abort run at any time.
        \n\n8. The robot should not physically damage the path and the box.
        \n\n9. The team that scores maximum points wins.
        \n\nHand Touch:
        \n\n1. If an operator touches the robot during run, this will be considered as a hand-touch and the robot must be put back at the last restart or checkpoint crossed. (Robot can be removed after completion of match, i.e. after placing the box.)
        \n\n2. The operator can take any number of hand touches with prior permission from judge. There is NO penalty for a hand touch (with prior permission) though the robot must be placed back at the start or last checkpoint crossed.
        \n\n3. Even if a participant takes a hand touch, the clock will keep running and will not be reset as the robot starts again from the previous restart point.
        \n\n4. If a robot ‘gets into trouble’ the operator can ask the judge for permission to take a hand touch and restart the robot at start or last checkpoint. If the operator touches the robot without prior permission of the judge during run time, 10 points will be deducted.
        \n\nGeneral Rules:
        \n\n1. Any team that is not ready at the time specified will be disqualified from the competition automatically. Programming of bot is not allowed once the competition starts.
        \n\n2. The machine will be checked for its safety before the match and will be discarded if found unsafe for other participants and spectators.
        \n\n3. It should not make any marks on the floor of the arena. Any robot found damaging the arena will be immediately disqualified.
        \n\n4. Only one member of the team is allowed to handle the robot.
        \n\n5. Participants are not allowed to keep anything inside the arena other than its autonomous robot.
        \n\n6. Laptops/personal computers are not allowed near the arena. Other Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, etc. devices must be switched off. The organizers hold the right to check for these devices and their usage.
        \n\n7. No robot can use any flammable, combustible, explosive or potentially dangerous processes.
        \n\n8. Only two switches can be present on the bot.
        \n\n9. The time measured by the organizers will be final and will be used for scoring the teams. Time measured by any contestant by any other means is not acceptable for scoring.
        \n\n10. Operator must wear socks.
        \n\n11. In case of any disputes/discrepancies, the organizers‟ decision will be final and binding. The organizers reserve the rights to change any or all of the above rules as they deem fit.
        \n\n12. Change in rules, if any, will be highlighted on the official MindSpark’17 website(www.mind-spark.org). Participants are requested to check the website regularly for updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_robowars">General:
        \n\n1. Participants should build a single robot.
        \n\n2. Robots will be tested for dimensions and safety before each match.
        \n\n3. Violation of rules will lead to disqualification of the respective team.
        \n\n4. Points will be deducted in case of multiple operators in a single match.
        \n\n5. The organizers reserve the rights to change any or all the above rules as they deem fit.
        \n\n6.In case of a match resulting in a tie, rematch of 2 minutes will be played. If further tie occurs team scoring highest points in first 3 minutes of the main match will be declared as a winner.
        \n\nCriteria for Victory:
        \n1. A robot is declared victorious if its opponent is immobilized.
        \n2. A robot will be declared immobile if it cannot show linear or rotational motion of at least one foot within a time of 30 seconds.
        \na) A robot with one side of its drive train disabled will not be counted immobilized, if it can demonstrate some degree of controlled movement.
        \nb) In case both the robots remain mobile after the end of the round then the winner will be decided subjectively.
        \n\n3. Points will be given based on aggression, damage, control and strategy, fall in the pit.
        \n\nAggression:
        \nAggression is judged by the frequency, severity, boldness and effectiveness of attacks deliberately initiated by the robot against its opponent. If a robot appears to have accidentally attacked an opponent, that act will not be considered Aggression.
        \n\nControl:
        \nControl means a robot can attack an opponent at its weakest point, use its weapons in the most effective way, avoid Arena Hazards, and minimize the damage caused by the opponent or its weapons.
        \n\nDamage:
        \nThrough deliberate action, a robot either directly, or indirectly using the Arena Hazards, reduces the functionality, effectiveness or defensibility of an opponent. Damage is not considered relevant if a robot inadvertently harms itself. Also, if a pressure vessel or a rapidly spinning device on a robot fragments, any damage to the opponent will not be considered "deliberate".
        \n\nStrategy:
        \nThe robot exhibits a combat plan that exploits the robot\'s strengths against the weaknesses of its opponent. Strategy is also defined as a robot exhibiting a deliberate defense plan that guards its weaknesses against the strengths of the opponent. Strategy can also involve using the Arena Hazards to gain an advantage.
        \n\nDisqualification:
        \n\n1. Robots intentionally damaging the wires of the opponent will be disqualified.
        \n\n2. Robots intentionally and extensively damaging the arena will be disqualified.
        \n\n3. If the wires of robot are cut because of its own strategy and if fail to repair within match time then the team will be disqualified.
        \n\nNote: There is no separate point allocation to the opposition in case if the bot is pushed or is stuck within the pit area.
        \n\nGame Field:
        \n1. Outer part of the field is a hexagon of side 3810mm (300 in) in having inner hexagon of side 298 in (actual game field).
        \n2. There is starting zone of size 750 x 750mm.
        \n3. Material used for game field will be made of plywood.
        \n4. There will be a safety wall provided around the game field. Height of safety wall will be 1.5 meters and it will be made up of fence and acrylic.
    \nDepth of the pit will be around 60mm-80mm and the size of each pit is 3824 x 100 mm2
    \n\nBot Dimensions and Fabrications:
    \n1. The robot should fit in the box of 750 mm x 750 mm x 1000 mm (l x b x h) always.
    \n\nNote: The external device used to control the robot or any external tank is not included in the size constraint.
    \n2. The robot should not exceed 40 kg of weight including the weight of pneumatic source/tank. If the tank is external, its weight would be considered 1.5 times its actual weight.
    \n3. Weight of wireless robots and robots having on-board power supply will be counted as 0.6 times the actual weight of robot.
    \n4. Weight of the remote controller and adapter will be considered.
    \n\nMotion of the Robot:
    \n1. Jumping and hopping is not allowed.
    \n2. Flying (using air-foil, helium balloons, ornithopters etc.) is not allowed.
    \n\nControl of Robot:
    \n1. Robot can have a wired or wireless control.
    \n2. Off board power supplies are allowed.
    \n3. If the machine is wired then the wire should remain slack under all circumstances during the competition. All the wires coming out of the machine should be stacked as a single unit. The wires should be properly insulated. Minimum length of wire should be 5 meters.
    \n4. In case of wireless control the case of frequency interference with other teams will not be considered for rematch or for result.
    \n5. The control wires should be drawn 1 meter above the ground.
    \n\nBattery and Power:
    \n1. The machine can be powered electrically only. Use of an IC engine in any form is not allowed. On board Batteries, must be sealed, immobilized-electrolyte types (such as gel cells, lithium, NiCad, NiMH, or dry cells).
    \n2. The electric voltage between 2 points anywhere in the machine should not be more than 36 V DC at any point of time. If a team is using AC voltage in any of its parts, then the voltage should not exceed 36 V AC at any point of time as well.
    \n3. All efforts must be made to protect battery terminals from a direct short and causing a battery fire, failure to do so will cause direct disqualification.
    \n4. Use of damaged, non-leak proof batteries may lead to disqualification.
    \n5. Special care should be taken to protect the on-board batteries.
    \n6. Change of battery will not be allowed during the match.
    \n\nHydraulics:
    \n1. Robot can use non-inflammable liquid to actuate hydraulic devices.
    \n2. All hydraulic components on-board a robot must be securely mounted.
    \n3. Special care must be taken while mounting pump, accumulator and armour to escape the robot.
    \n4. Whole hydraulic systems should be leak proof. Maximum allowed pressure is 8 bars.
    \n5. Participant must be able to indicate the used pressure with integrated or temporarily fitted pressure gauge.
    \n\nPneumatics:
    \n1. Robot can use pressurized non-inflammable gases to actuate pneumatic devices. Maximum allowed outlet pressure is 8 bars. The storage tank and pressure regulators used by teams need to be certified. Teams using pneumatics are required to produce the Safety and Security letters at the registration Desk at the venue. Failing to do so will lead to direct disqualification.
    \n2. Participants must be able to indicate the used pressure with integrated or temporarily fitted pressure gauge. Also, there should be provision to check the cylinder pressure on the bot.
    \n3. You must have a safe way of refilling the system and determining the on-board pressure. All pneumatic components on board a robot must be securely mounted. Care must be taken while mounting the pressure vessel and armor to ensure that if ruptured it will not escape the robot. Failing to do so will lead to direct disqualification.
    \n\nWeapons:
    \nRobots can have any kind of cutters, flippers, saws, lifting devices, spinning hammers as weapons. Exceptions and Limitations for weapons:
    \n1. Liquid projectiles.
    \n2. Any kind of inflammable liquid.
    \n3. Flame-based weapons.
    \n4. Any kind of explosive or intentionally ignited solid or potentially ignitable solid.
    \n5. Nets, tape, glue, chains or any other entanglement device.
    \n6. High power magnets or electromagnets.
    \n7. Radio jamming, lasers, tesla coils, or any other high-voltage device.
    \n8. Tethered or un-tethered projectiles.
    \n9. Spinning weapons which do not meet the arena at any point of time are allowed. In any case the arena should not be damaged by any bot.
    \n\nSafety Rules:
    \n1. Special care should be taken to protect the on-board batteries and pneumatics, robot without proper protection will not be allowed to compete.
    \n2. Robots must be activated in the arena or with expressed consent of the event coordinators.
    \n3. All weapons must have a safety cover on any sharp edges.
    \n4. All participants build and operate robots at their own risk. Please take care to not hurt yourself or others when building, testing and competing. Organizers will not be responsible for any injuries to operator or team members.
    \nA robot that is deemed unsafe by the judges after the match has begun will be disqualified and therefore declared the loser. The match will be immediately halted and the opponent will be awarded a win.
    \nJudges and Event Head\'s decision will be treated as final and binding to all.
    </string>
    <string name="event_rules_dog_fight">Violations:
        \n• At any time, if the wire is seen to be pulling the robot, it will be considered as violation.
        \n• Any part of the robot extending out of arena will lead to violation.
        \n• Hand touch without prior permission will cause violation.
        \n• Any part of MR extending in AR zone (Except while depositing message Block) and any part of AR in MR zone will be considered as violation.
        \n• MR of one team touching MR of another team will be considered as violation (except when in the Grey Zone).
        \n• MR running in opponent"\'"s area beyond grey zone will be violation. Every violation will cost the team „-5‟ points. Five points will be deducted for every violation.
        \n\nRestart Rules:
        \n• For both robots unlimited number of retry will be allowed.
        \n• The operators will first have to ask the judges for a hand-touch/restart and take the hand-touch/restart only when allowed. The M.R. or A.R. can restart from either start zone or checkpoint after the hand touch. Once the team has cleared the checkpoint, the operators are allowed to choose whether they want to restart from the start zone or the check point.
        \n• The orientation of the robot after the hand-touch will be decided by the judges. The timer will continue to run in this period and the other team will continue.
        \n\nGeneral Rules:
        \n• If the machine is stuck or rendered immobile and cannot proceed further on its own, the hand touch will be allowed. If both the robots are stuck, then hand touch is allowed only when both the manual operators want to take hand touch. MR can pick the message block only after AR deposits the message block in the area with yellow border.
        \n• In case, the wires of the Manual Robots of both the teams getting entangled with each other, the judges will call for a time-out in the game. The Manual Robots will be restarted from the same position after the wires have been sorted out and the autonomous robot will continue its work till it calls for retry but retry will not be given till the wires of manual robots have been sorted out.
        \n• At each hand-touch, all the objects in touch with the robot of that team (except for the ones already deposited) will be returned to their original positions.
        \n• Objects will be placed in original position after retry if they were wrongly placed.
        \n• Any part of MR is not allowed to enter in AR zone except while transferring the message Block. Any attempt to enter the zone or touch or damage an autonomous robot deliberately will lead to disqualification of the team.
        \n• Maximum Five violations are allowed, any violations after that would lead to disqualification.
        \n• Any team that is not ready at the specified time will be disqualified from the competition.
        \n• The robot will be checked for its safety before the match and will be discarded if found unsafe for other participants, spectators or arena.
        \n• The name of your robot must be prominently displayed on the robot.
        \n• Operators can’t step on arena unless permitted by judges.
        \n• MR operator has to operate from outside the arena.
        \n• AR operator must wear socks.
        \n• Judges‟ decision shall be treated as final and binding to all.
        \n• The organizers reserve the rights to change any or all of the above rules as they deem fit.
        \n• Change in rules, if any, will be highlighted on the website. Readymade Robots are not allowed, but readymade sensors kits are allowed.
        \n\nSafety Rules:
        \n• Use of fire, water, spraying chemicals is not allowed. This would lead to immediate disqualification of the team.
        \n• The robot can block the opponent’s robot only by pushing/pulling or lifting the opponent’s robot. However, the robot is not allowed to destroy the opponent’s robot.
        \n• NO mechanism should be used to attack the opponent’s robot or cause any harm to the opponent’s robot or its wires or to the arena. Doing so will lead to disqualification. The judges’ decision in this matter will be final and binding.
        \n• Participants can expect that their robots may be pushed or lifted and hence should be balanced enough to bear the fall.
        \n• Jamming of RF control signals is NOT allowed. Teams MUST inform the judges about the RF signals involved in its robot during the Registration of the robot and before the start of the game.
        \n• No deliberate damage must be done to the arena. The mechanism to carry objects should NOT damage them and any part of the Arena. Any damage caused after prior warning has been given will lead to disqualification.
        \n• Decision of Mind Spark team will be considered as final in case of any dispute.
        \n\nMiscellaneous:
        \n• Total game field is of the size 5000x5000 mm.
        \n• Game field is surrounded by walls of 20 mm thick and 200 mm height.
        \n• Arena is symmetrically divided into two ideal parts, Blue and Red except the common area in MR zone.
        \n• In each part, there is a MR zone and an AR zone.
        \n• All objects and arena parts will be coated with vinyl sheets having respective colours.
        \n• Internal wall will have thickness 20mm.
        \n• Thickness of all the walls subject to change without any prior notice.
        \n• Colour shades of the arena and the objects subject to vary within acceptable limits.
        \n• The dimensions of static objects in the Arena may change subject to manufacturing difficulties.
        \n• 5% bidirectional tolerance applicable to all the static objects in the arena.
        \n• Any change in the arena will be informed to participants and will be highlighted on website.
        \n\nMachine Specifications:
        \n• Only one MR and one AR is allowed. The Robot can’t separate into two connected by just a wire.
        \n• The combined weight of the MR and AR (including batteries and Pneumatic reservoirs) should NOT exceed 15 kg.
        \n• The MR should fit in the box of 500*500*500mm. It should fit in the MR Start zone at the beginning of the game.
        \n• AR dimensions should not be more than 250*250mm. Use of Automatic Robots is not mandatory for task (only MR can participate). No restriction on height of AR.
        \n• The dimensions of the Robot may change during the course of the game.
        \n• The MR can use on-board power supply or external power supply.
        \n• AR must use on-board power supply only.
        \n• Participants will be provided with a 230 V AC power source and a standard 32V variable/2A DC power supply. Cost of any damage done will have to be borne by the participants. The voltage at any point on any of the robot should not exceed 24V DC. Participants can also bring their own power supply in this case maximum current and voltage limit are 5 amperes and 24 volts respectively. The voltage and current should not exceed this limit.
        \n• Pressure of the pressurized non-inflammable gases in the Pneumatic Reservoir should not exceed 5 bar at any stage of the match.
        \n• The storage tank and pressure regulators used by teams need to be certified and teams using pneumatics are required to produce the Safety and Security letters at the Registration Desk at the venue. Failing to do so will lead to direct disqualification. • Participants must be able to indicate the used pressure with integrated or temporarily fitted pressure gauge. Also, there should be provision to check the cylinder pressure on the bot.
        \n• You must have a safe way of refilling the system and determining the on-board pressure.
        \n• All pneumatic components on board a robot must be securely mounted. Care must be taken while mounting the pressure vessel and armour to ensure that if ruptured it will not escape the robot.
        \n• The control for the machines can be wired or wireless. There can be only one Manual Operator for the MR and only one Autonomous operator for the AR in a particular match. In case of Wireless Controls, the participants are requested to use dual channel remotes so that there are no issues of interference during the event. The remote control and wires will not be included in the machine sizes.
        \n• The minimum length of wire extending from the robot up to remote should be 4 meter. The wire should always be in slacked condition.
        \n\nCompetition Structure:
        \n\nElimination Round:
        \n• Each team will be given total time of 4 minutes. Only one team will play at a time. They have to complete the task and score maximum points during this round.
        \n• Teams will be ranked according to following preferences:
        \n• Task completion.
        \n• Scores in the elimination round.
        \n• The top 16 teams will qualify for the next round.
        \n• The score of the team from the elimination round will not be considered in the next round.
        \n\nKnock-Out Round:
        \n The knock-out round will start with top 16 teams. Each match will last for maximum 4 minutes.
        \n• A team, once registered, cannot register again, even with a different name.
        \n• A team may consist of a maximum of 5 members.
        \n• All students with a valid identity card of their respective educational institutes are eligible to participate.
        \n• Teams will be required to show the I-Cards of all of its team members during the matches.
        \n• A team may consist of members from different educational institutes.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_bot_wrestling">GENERAL RULES:
        \n1. Any team that is not ready at the time specified will be disqualified from the competition automatically.
        \n2. The machine will be checked for its safety before each match and will be discarded if found unsafe for other participants and spectators.
        \n3. Team members will not be allowed to step in the arena. Only organizers are allowed in any situation. The team will be disqualified if any of the team members steps on the arena without the approval of the presiding organizers.
        \n4. Only one member of the team is allowed to handle and operate the robot.
        \n5. Participants are not allowed to keep anything inside the arena other than its robot.
        \n6. No robot is allowed to use any flammable, combustible, explosive or potentially dangerous processes.
        \n7. Proper protection majors from short-circuiting of batteries are required to be taken by participants for the safety of everyone present at arena.
        \n8. The time measured by the organizers will be final and will be used for scoring the teams. Time measured by any contestant by any other means is not acceptable for scoring.
        \n9. In case of any disputes/discrepancies, the organizers’ decision will be final and binding. The organizers reserve the rights to change any or all of the above rules as they deem fit. Change in rules, if any, will be highlighted on the website and notified to the registered teams.
        \n\nHand Touch:
        \n1. No hand touches are allowed in between the matches unless both the operators of the respective robots want a restart.
        \n2. If a restart is taken then both the robots will be placed back in their respective starting zones.
        \n3. Even if a participant takes a hand touch, the clock will keep running and will not be reset as the robots start again from the starting points.
        \n\nRULES:
        \n1. Qualifier Matches: Each match consists of 1 round.
        \n2. Knockout Matches: Each match consists best of 3 rounds.
        \n3. Before the match 1minute setting time will be given. The run time clock will commence after that 1minute time limit even if the handler is still making adjustments to the robots.
        \n4. 30 seconds setting time will be given in between the rounds.
        \n5. The robot must start from the starting point. The operator may abort run at any time.
        \n6. In such a case, the opposite team will be declared as the winner.
        \n7. No hand touches are allowed in between the matches unless both the operators of the respective robots want a restart.
        \n8. Use of Jammers is not allowed. Participants found violating this rule will be disqualified from the competition.
        \n9. There can be interference problems related to RF modules in case you are using them.
        \n10. It is the responsibility of the participants to overcome it. Organizers are not responsible for it.
        \n11. Judges’ decision shall be treated as final and binding on all.
        \n12. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the official MindSpark’17 (www.mind-spark.org) website regularly for update.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_virtual_robotics">1. The contestants must carry identification cards of their respective educational institutes.
        \n\n2. Contestants from different educational institutes can participate as a team.
        \n\n3. Contestants can register multiple times provided that no two designs belong to the same theme, however each registration will be treated separately.
        \n\n4. The decision of the Judges’ and the event heads’ will be final and binding to all.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_the_amazing_race">1. The team has complete discretion in formulating and applying all rules and penalties. These rules may be modified or altered at the discretion of the Amazing Race Team, as required.
        \n\n2. The Participants are expected to follow all the rules and regulations laid by the Motor Vehicles Act. Violations will result in disqualification of the team. Each team would only be allowed to take part after producing a valid permanent driving license.
        \n\n3. If any information provided by the team is found to be false or incorrect, the team will be disqualified.
        \n\n4. The timings recorded by The Amazing Race volunteers would be deemed final and any arguments with respect to the recorded time will not be entertained.
        \n\n5. Physical damage or irresponsible handling such as tearing in part or totality of the checkpoint list will lead to disqualification.
        \n\n6. The team spotted littering or throwing garbage along the route of the race, or altering or tampering unnecessarily with any of the natural surroundings will be disqualified.
        \n\n7. No outside (non- team member) support is allowed between the start and finish lines of the race. Only the team is allowed in any official race area. 8. Event organizers reserve the right to prohibit a competitor from starting or finishing any segment of the Race on medical grounds. Any such decision of the Race committee is final and binding to everyone involved. 9. No person can be a part of multiple teams for this event. In case of any clashes, the organizers of the event will not be responsible. 10. No two teams will be allowed to work on a particular problem together. It is a competition and ultimately each one has to compete with each other. 11. Participants are requested to strictly follow traffic rules. In case of traffic violation, The Amazing Race team will not help/ be responsible for any further consequences. 12. The Amazing Race Team reserves the right to impose time penalties or to disqualify teams for violation of any of these rules, contrary to the best interest of the event. Failure of any team member or a team to immediately and respectfully comply, with any direction or decision of the organizers, will result in disqualification of the team. 13. MindSpark’17 team will not be responsible for any damage done to people, property or vehicles. The damage has to be reimbursed by the participant in concern. 14. Some essentials for the event include smartphones with cameras, and other such necessary applications. These will be beneficial for the participants during the event and the participants are requested to carry these with them on their personal responsibility. 15. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for further updates.</string><string name="event_rules_bull_run">1. This event shall be an open-internet event. Therefore, use of mobile phones and other electronic devices are permitted.
        \n\n2. At the start of Round 1, participants shall be given ₹20,00,000/-, in virtual money, and the same ₹20,00,000/- shall be given for Round 2. NOTE: If you have money left from Round 1, it will NOT be added in Round 2.
        \n\n3. Based on the information that will be given to the participants, they will have to buy and/or sell shares of various companies, to earn maximum profits.
        \n\n4. Round 1 will be taking place in various slots. Therefore, participants must ensure that their contact information is valid, so as to allow us to inform you well in advance regarding any changes to the timings of your slots.
        \n\n5.This event will feature a Live Simulation of the stock market; wherein constant updates will be given to the participants during the event. Participants must check these updates and accordingly, make their necessary decisions.
        \n\n6. Participants must always have their College ID and their registration receipts with them, and must be shown if asked.
        \n\n7. In case of any dispute, the decision of both the judges and the organizers shall be final and binding to all.
        \n\n8. Rules may be changed without any prior intimation to the participants. Therefore, participants must ensure that they regularly check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) for all updates.
        \n\n9. All undergraduate and postgraduate students are allowed to participate.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_bidzkreig_1">1. Participants have to bring their valid College ID cards and the registration receipt during reporting.
        \n\n2. Participants are allowed to use mobile phones or calculators in the second round.
        \n\n3. Cross college teams are allowed. However, one person cannot be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
        \n\n4. Structure of the event may be changed without prior intimation.Participants are, therefore, requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_bidzkreig_2">1. A team will be disqualified if it uses the given amount of money and does not have 5 players in the squad.
        \n\n2. Once a team buys the required players for a certain position, they cannot bid for another player for the same position.
        \n\n3. A team can name one of their player as captain which will multiply the chosen player\'s rating by 2.
        \n\n4. Each team will start with a starting budget of $ 50 million. The draw of the players will be random.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_lan_slam">1. Counter Strike: Global Offensive will be played in competitive mode.
        \n\n2. Participants must not mishandle the computer system. Any damage caused, will lead to direct disqualification and the cost of the damage if any will be paid by the participants.
        \n\n3.Use of cheats or any deceitful means will lead to immediate team disqualification.
        \n\n4. Use of offensive language by any participant will lead to team disqualification.
        \n\n5. Selection procedure will be decided by the organizers and their decision will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n6. Participants are requested to bring their own headphones/earphones to the event. Consoles, mouse and personal keyboards are also allowed.
        \n\n7. Time slots will be given and participants are expected to follow it strictly. If the teams are not punctual and are not present on time, they will be disqualified and the opposing teams will be given a bye.
        \n\n8. Participants are expected to give their correct contact details, so as to inform them about the round timings.
        \n\n9. Some match rules will be decided by the event heads at that time and will be declared on the spot.
        \n\n10. A match draw will be decided by an extra round. Whichever team wins this round will be declared the winner.
        \n\n11. Team members can be from same as well as different institutes. But there can be no change of players within teams during the rounds and one person cannot be a part of multiple teams.
        \n\n12. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are, therefore, requested to check our official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_flash">1. Post processing of pictures is allowed.
        \n\n2. You need to bring your own camera, mobile or any other accessory you need during the event.
        \n\n3. Participants are allowed to participate in more than one category for this event.
        \n\n4. For categories 3 and 4, unprocessed files must also be submitted along with the gear (mobile model/camera model + lens + exifs) used mentioned.
        \n\n5. The entries would be judged based on composition, creativity, and post processing.
        \n\n6. The event head/coordinators have the right to deny the participant from participating in the event if participants break above mentioned rules.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_chakravyuh">1. Quiz master’s decision will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n2. Use of any form of electronic media is strictly not allowed. Any team found in violation will be disqualified on the spot.
        \n\n3. Participants must bring their registration receipts and valid college IDs (For college students) or any valid ID (For others) while coming to the event.
        \n\n4. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.
        \n\n5. In case of any disputes, the decision taken by the organizers will be considered final and binding to all.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_indikya">1. Quiz master’s decision will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n2. Use of any form of electronic media is strictly not allowed. Any team found in violation will be disqualified on the spot.
        \n\n3. Participants must bring their registration receipts and valid college IDs while coming to the event.
        \n\n4. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.
        \n\n5. In case of any disputes, the decision taken by the organizers will be considered final and binding to all.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_torquest">1. Quiz master’s decision will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n2. Use of any form of electronic media is strictly not allowed. Any team found in violation will be disqualified on the spot.
        \n\n3. Participants must bring their registration receipts and valid college IDs while coming to the event.
        \n\n4. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.
        \n\n5.In case of any disputes, the decision taken by the organizers will be considered final and binding to all.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_genius_jr">1. Teams are expected to maintain decorum. MindSpark team reserves the right to disqualify any team found misbehaving.
        \n\n2. In case of any disputes, the decision of event heads and judges will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n3. Rules of the event may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.
        \n\n4. Participants must carry their school ID card and the registration receipt.
        \n\n5. Participants must be present on time at the given venue. Late entries will not be entertained.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_sudoku">1. Overwriting is not allowed.
        \n\n2. Rough papers will not be permitted in the event.
        \n\n3. Decisions taken by event heads and coordinators are final and binding and cannot be challenged.
        \n\n4. A valid ID card and the receipt for the event must be carried to the event.
        \n\n5. Rules and structure of the event may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are therefore requested to check the official MindSpark\'17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_googler">1. Teams are expected to maintain decorum. We reserve the right to disqualify any team found misbehaving.
        \n\n2. In case of any disputes, the decision of event heads and judges will be final and binding to all.
        \n\n3. Rules of the event may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.
        \n\n4. Participants must carry their college ID card and the registration receipt.
        \n\n5. Participants must be present on time at the given venue. Late entries will not be entertained.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_ham">1. Participants must carry their ID-Card during the workshop.
        \n\n2. Participants must be punctual for all reporting times.
        \n\n3. Structure and theory covered may be changed according to constraints. Please check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) for updates regularly.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_tux">1. Participants must carry their registration receipt and a valid ID card at all times during the workshop.
        \n\n2. Participants must be punctual for all reporting times. Sessions may begin without participants if they are late.
        \n\n3. If any damage occurs to the machines, participants may be asked to refund the cost of repairs.
        \n\n4. Organizers are not responsible for any harm caused to participants due to their own negligence.
        \n\n5. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_stareway_to_heaven">1. Participants are expected to carry a valid ID card and a receipt of registration at all times during the workshop.
        \n\n2. The participants are requested to check the official MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for further updates.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_cnc_lathe">1.Participants must carry theirregistration receipt and a valid ID-Card at all times during the workshop. It will be helpful (not necessary) if participants acquire some fundamental knowledge about NC/CNC through resources like books/internet. You can refer some notes from official website of MindSpark’17 (www.mind-spark.org).
        \n\n2. Participants must be punctual at all reporting times. Sessions will begin without participants if they are late.
        \n\n3. If any damage occurs to the machines/institute property, participants may be asked to refund the cost of repairs.
        \n\n4. Organizers are not responsible for any harm caused to participants due to their own negligence. Participants have to take care of their own safety.
        \n\n5. Structure and theory covered may be changed according to constraints. Please check the official MindSpark’17 website(www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.
        \n\n6. Rules may be changed without prior intimation. For further updates, participants are requested to check the MindSpark’17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.
        \n\n7. In case of any disputes, the decision of the organizers will be final and binding to all.</string>
    <string name="event_rules_virtual_labs">1.Participants are required to carry their respective institution’s identity card.
        \n\n2.Rules may be changed without prior intimation. Participants are, therefore, requested to check the official MindSpark\'17 website (www.mind-spark.org) regularly for updates.</string>

    <string name="event_tafs_epitome">Team size : Max. 3 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹150/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_conquest">Team Size : Max. of 3 members per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_metropolis">Team Size : Max. 4 participants per team
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹100/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_id_civil">Team Size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹50/- per team</string>

    <string name="event_tafs_assemblix">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹100/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_id_2d">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_id_3d">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_mechtrix">Team Size : Max. 4 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹150/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_turnament">Team size : Individual participation.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹50/- per team.</string>

    <string name="event_tafs_code_junkie">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_code_junkie_pp">Team size : Max. of 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_xterminate">Team size : Only 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_retracer">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_predict_x">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 100/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_hackathon2.0">Team size : Max. 3 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹150/- per team.</string>

    <string name="event_tafs_circuit_fixer_1">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_circuit_fixer_2">Team size : Max. of 2 participants per team
        \nRegistration fee : ₹50/- per team</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_encrypto">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_microapps">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 50/- per team</string>

    <string name="event_tafs_on_the_etch">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nParticipation Fee : ₹ 50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_dexters_lab">Team Size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 50/- per team.</string>

    <string name="event_tafs_wheelomation">Team Size : Minimum 2 and maximum 5 participants per team
        \nRegistration fees : ₹250/- per team</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_the_wright_turn_glider">Team size : Maximum 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹50/- per team</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_the_wright_turn_rc_plane">Team size : Maximum 5 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹250/- per team</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_aqualympics">Team size : Max. 4 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹200/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_contraption">Team size : Max. 4 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 200/- per team.</string>

    <string name="event_tafs_byldan">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team
        \nRegistration fee : ₹50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_ppt_comp_it">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_ppt_mech_prod_meta">PPT Mech/Prod/Meta</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_ppt_eei">PPT ENI</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_ppt_civil">PPT Civil</string>

    <string name="event_tafs_search_n_destroy">Team Size : Max. 5 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹250/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_robowars">Team size : Max. 5 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹250/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_dog_fight">Team size : Max. 5 participants per team.
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹250/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_bot_wrestling">Team size : Max. of 4 members per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹200/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_virtual_robotics">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nParticipation Fee : ₹ 50/- per team.</string>

    <string name="event_tafs_the_amazing_race">Team Size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹100/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_bull_run">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 100/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_bidzkreig_1">Team Size : Max. 2 members per team
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹ 100/- per team</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_bidzkreig_2">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 100/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_lan_slam">Team Size : Only 4 participants per team.
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹200/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_flash">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹50/- per team.</string>

    <string name="event_tafs_chakravyuh">Team Size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_indikya">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹ 100/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_torquest">Team Size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹50/- per team.</string>

    <string name="event_tafs_genius_jr">Team Size : Max. 2 participants per team.
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹ 100/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_sudoku">Team size : Individual participation only.
        \nRegistration fee : ₹50/- per team.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_googler">Team size : Max. 2 participants per team
        \nRegistration fee : ₹50/- per team.</string>

    <string name="event_tafs_ham">Team Size : Individual event.
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹100/- per individual.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_tux">Team Size : Individual event.
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹100/- per individual.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_stareway_to_heaven">Team Size : Individual event.
        \nRegistration Fee : ‘Free for all’ event.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_cnc_lathe">Team Size : Individual event.
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹200/- per individual.</string>
    <string name="event_tafs_virtual_labs">Team Size : Individual event.
        \nRegistration Fee : ₹100/- per individual.</string>


    <string name="event_heads_epitome">Bhakti Balaji Rudrawar : +91 9405392661
        \nNarayani S.A. : +91 9767390238
        \nEmail ID : epitome@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_conquest">Pranjali Patil : +91 91566 04126
        \nChetan Patil : +91 84219 51547
        \nEmail ID : conquest@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_metropolis">Sohel Fakir : +91 8484954779
        \nShubham Phulgirkar : +91 9167020472
        \nEmail ID : metropolis@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_id_civil">Aditya Varma : +91 73856 71821
        \nKalyani Bhadane : +91 91752 65618
        \nEmail ID : idcivil@mind-spark.org</string>

    <string name="event_heads_assemblix">Avinash Acchra : +91 96736 17898
        \nTanay Atpadkar : +91 73505 35333
        \nEmail ID : assemblix@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_id_2d">Prajakta Pangare : +91 90750 21766
        \nRajvardhan Nalawade : +91 93266 33594
        \nEmail ID : id2d@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_id_3d">Akash Kolte : +91 88886 08038
        \nManisha Gangurde : +91 77092 77401
        \nEmail ID : id3d@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_mechtrix">Abhishek Desai : +91 99214 72043
        \nVishakha Orke : +91 77094 85533
        \nEmail ID : mechtrix@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_turnament">Shubham Chaudhari : +91 8879885934
        \nNilesh Patil : +91 8149098553
        \nEmail ID : turnament@mind-spark.org</string>

    <string name="event_heads_code_junkie">Mokshada Mundada : +91 96651 85538
        \nTejaswini Khambe : +91 94056 77060
        \nEmail ID : codejunkie1@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_code_junkie_pp">Sumedh Pendurkar : +91 90117 41004
        \nShivkumar Patil : +91 99601 16656
        \nEmail ID : codejunkie2@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_xterminate">Tejas Nayak : +91 84461 04030
        \nAkash Patil : +91 94044 17257
        \nEmail ID : xterminate@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_retracer">Balasubramanian M. : +91 75884 75928
        \nVivek Bhave : +91 95274 80727
        \nEmail ID : retracer@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_predict_x">Ameya Apte : +91 75882 86543
        \nVarad Ghodake : +91 94048 63327</string>
    <string name="event_heads_hackathon2.0">Chirag Joshi : +91 90280 80903
        \nPushan Gore : +91 83086 18739
        \nEmail ID : hackathon@mind-spark.org</string>

    <string name="event_heads_circuit_fixer_1">Kasturi Mahatme : +91 91455 35643
        \nAshish Pisal : +91 89838 98624
        \nEmail ID : circuitfixer1@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_circuit_fixer_2">Aditi Gadakari : +91 83080 04715
        \nAdit Pradhan : +91 90103 47280
        \nEmail ID : circuitfixer2@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_encrypto">Rocky Jose : +91 83799 48402
        \nTejas Thakre : +91 83083 10127
        \nEmail ID : encrypto@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_microapps">Pradnya Sabale : +91 83799 25831
        \nKoshy Thomas : +91 94055 62304
        \nEmail ID : microapps@mind-spark.org</string>

    <string name="event_heads_on_the_etch">Revathi Ambekar : +91 97667 88860
        \nSanket Ghanwat : +91 87963 23532
        \nEmail ID : etch@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_dexters_lab">Divyansh Kasture : +91 94237 04853
        \nKasturi Revatkar : +91 94218 05960
        \nEmail ID : dexterslab@mind-spark.org</string>

    <string name="event_heads_wheelomation">Naeem Sayyad : +91 96575 35794
        \nAmogh Patnaik : +91 99872 50260
        \nEmail ID : wheelomation@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_the_wright_turn_glider">Aneri Desai : +91 90493 25703
        \nAnmol Jain : +91 95616 07929
        \nEmail ID : wrightturn@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_the_wright_turn_rc_plane">Aneri Desai : +91 90493 25703
        \nAnmol Jain : +91 95616 07929
        \nEmail ID : wrightturn@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_aqualympics">Atharva Joshi : +91 75887 46427
        \nAshish Hawale : +91 89834 21625
        \nEmail ID :aqualympics@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_contraption">Shubham Sawalkar : +91 73853 95488
        \nRohit Shelke : +91 70382 59294
        \nEmail ID : contraption@mind-spark.org</string>

    <string name="event_heads_byldan">Kartik Chaudhari : +91 86986 73422
        \nShreyas Dhoot : +91 91674 93393
        \nEmail ID : byldan@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_ppt_comp_it">Akash Zure : +91 73854 64072
        \nEmail ID : ppt_compit@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_ppt_mech_prod_meta">Mihir Date : +91 70280 73009
        \nEmail ID : ppt_mechprodmeta@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_ppt_eei">Ajinkya Phanse : +91 96239 49366
        \nEmail : ppt_eei@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_ppt_civil">Rushikesh Ingole : +91 80074 40679
        \nEmail ID : ppt civil@mind-spark.org</string>

    <string name="event_heads_search_n_destroy">Anand Sabne : +91 94235 00578
        \nMansi Kabade : +91 94220 16944
        \nEmail ID : searchndestroy@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_robowars">Anirudh Peri : +91 98676 12443
        \nYunus Pirjade : +91 96378 80658
        \nEmail ID : robowars@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_dog_fight">Abhishek Jadhav : +91 91689 80045
        \nVaishnavi Hardikar : +91 95529 30478
        \nShreejit Deshmukh : +91 86002 39230
        \nEmail ID : dogfight@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_bot_wrestling">Hrishikesh Kale : +91 94201 72305
        \nBhushan Rane : +91 94040 31297
        \nEmail ID : botwrestling@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_virtual_robotics">Aditya Khandekar : +91 88883 00975
        \nMansi Kabade : +91 94220 16944
        \nEmail ID : searchndestroy@mind-spark.org</string>

    <string name="event_heads_the_amazing_race">Suruchi Jadhav : +91 99221 51351
        \nNipun Jain : +91 85540 54445
        \nMahesh Bhakre : +91 72185 58173
        \nEmail id : amazingrace@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_bull_run">Yashaswi Ranjan : +91 80970 08914
        \nYash Pawar : +91 77750 34594
        \nEmail ID : bullrun@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_bidzkreig_1">Akash Mhetre : +91 86985 5791
        \nShubham Bhutada : +91 94047 37707
        \nEmail ID : bidzkrieg@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_bidzkreig_2">Ayush Moitra : +91 99875 40465
        \nKetan Hukare : +91 97693 68197
        \nEmail-ID : bidzkreig2@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_lan_slam">Shubham Mukkawar : +91 78750 86259
        \nDurgesh Bhadane : +91 86987 11406
        \nEmail ID : lanslam@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_flash">Sarang Bhat : +91 97028 56956 / +91 70666 33904
        \nAbdul Muqeet : +91 77096 07359
        \nEmail ID : flash@mind-spark.org</string>

    <string name="event_heads_chakravyuh">Dhananjay Jagtap : +91 94235 07558
        \nEmail ID : chakravyuh@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_indikya">Divij Ghose : +91 95270 48212
        \nEmail ID : indikya@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_torquest">Vrushabh Gudade : +91 91758 43438
        \nEmail ID : torquest@mind-spark.org</string>

    <string name="event_heads_genius_jr">Vivek Shete : +91 77749 91134
        \nPrem Singh : +91 86238 98893
        \nPrathamesh Jagtap : +91 75883 74327
        \nEmail ID : geniusjr@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_sudoku">Ananya A K : +91 80976 21282
        \nVaishnavi Ranade : +91 91300 94910
        \nEmail ID : sudoku@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_googler">Rushikesh D. Patangrao : +91 84839 85155
        \nRushi Deshpande : +91 94208 59810
        \nEmail ID : googler@mind-spark.org</string>

    <string name="event_heads_ham">Abruti Panda : +91 9923119512
        \nPrathamesh Mandke : +91 7755908804
        \nEmail ID : ham@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_tux">Shubham Khandelwal : +91 82378 24147
        \nEmail ID : tux@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_stareway_to_heaven">Siddharth Gundecha : +91 8180916339
        \nEmail ID : starewaytoheaven@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_cnc_lathe">Vinayak Jadhav : +91 8082763528
        \nKrishnaly Baheti : +91 84461 23514
        \nEmail ID : cnclathe@mind-spark.org</string>
    <string name="event_heads_virtual_labs">Shreyash Kumath : +91 91300 05037
        \nEmail ID : virtuallab@mind-spark.org</string>

    <string name="workshop_title_ethical_hacking">Ethical Hacking</string>
    <string name="workshop_title_hovercraft">Hovercraft</string>
    <string name="workshop_title_android_app_development">Android App Development</string>
    <string name="workshop_title_fantastic_four">Fantastic Four</string>
    <string name="workshop_title_3d_game_designing_and_virtual_reality">3D Game Designing and Virtual Reality</string>
    <string name="workshop_title_creo_workshop">Creo Workshop</string>
    <string name="workshop_title_advanced_iot">Advanced IoT</string>
    <string name="workshop_title_hello_to_hired">Hello-to-Hired</string>
    <string name="workshop_title_rc_nitro_car">RC Nitro Car</string>
    <string name="workshop_title_multi_touch_and_gesture_computing">Multi-Touch And Gesture Computing</string>


    <string name="workshop_introduction_ethical_hacking">Ethical Hacking Workshop is 2 days workshop (max. 8 hours/day) by Sangeet Chopra. This workshop will be divided into 4 sessions partici-pants are introduced to various concepts of ethical hacking. The Partici-pants will get introduced and informed about various case studies in the subject. </string>
    <string name="workshop_introduction_hovercraft">The Hovercraft workshop trains students to design, fabricate and test run their own mini Radio controlled hovercrafts and make them practically understand the aerodynamics, electronics and instrumentation principles involved in hovercraft design. Get into the world of most advanced future machines in the automobile sector which can easily move on land and water.</string>
    <string name="workshop_introduction_android_app_development">THIS IS A TWO DAY WORKSHOP IN WHICH WE FOCUS ON BOTH FRONT AND BACK END OF (Full stack) APP DEVELOPMENT, WITH AN AIM OF DEVELOPING A WORKING APP AT THE END OF TWO DAYS. THE WORKSHOP WILL TAKE A TOTAL OF 16 HRS WHICH IS DIVIDED INTO TWO PARTS THAT IS 8 HRS DAILY. EACH DAY IS FURTHER DIVIDED INTO PRE AND POST LUNCH SESSION.</string>
    <string name="workshop_introduction_fantastic_four">FANTASTIC FOUR ROBOTICS IS TWO DAYS WORKSHOP IN WHICH OUR TRAINER FOCUSES ON INTRODUCING PARTICIPANTS TO THE WORLD OF ROBOTICS. THIS WORKSHOP WILL TAKE TOTAL TIME OF MAX.16 HRS WHICH IS DIVIDED INTO TWO PARTS THAT IS 8 HRS PER DAY. THIS WORKSHOP IS DIVIDED INTO FOUR DIFFERENT SESSION IN WHICH PARTICIPANTS ARE INTRODUCED TO VARIOUS CONCEPTS RELATED TO ROBOTICS, MICROCONTROLLERS, IDE PROGRAMMING, BLUE-TOOTH MODULE, ETC. PRACTICALLY. </string>
    <string name="workshop_introduction_3d_game_designing_and_virtual_reality">3D gaming is interactive computer entertainment that is graphically presented in the three dimensions of height, width and depth; the addi-tion of depth to 2D gaming enabled the exploration of virtual worlds with more realistic representation. This 2-days workshop imparts the basics of Unity system for 3D game development. Unity is a cross-platform game engine developed by Unity Technologies and used to develop video games for PC, consoles, mobile devices and websites.
        \nInterest in Virtual Reality (VR) is growing – don’t miss your chance to catch it ahead of the curve. With major brands like YouTube and Face-book developing platforms to support 360 video, VR is becoming more and more accessible to the general public. Expand your digital pres-ence by immersing your audience in an interactive, hands-on environ-ment.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_introduction_creo_workshop">Explore the latest version of creo before anyone else. Learn modelling using CREO 4.0. This curriculum is structured to provide as much exposure to industry best practices and to the variety of models and activities that occur in product development as is possible. There are 12 exercises and each exercise is typically organized with a hands-on activity to explain the concepts, then a practice model to enforce the learning of the concepts and then a final skills assessment activity that provides another model to demonstrate the acquired skills.
        \nTeachers who are in the classroom are the best practitioners for determining how to integrate curriculum like this into the normal classroom curriculum so that it can enhance and reinforce the standards based curriculum that is being taught. This curriculum is engaging and inspiring and gives students hands-on, active learning experiences. It has been developed and tested in real classrooms and shown to engage and inspire students.
        \nPTC Inc. proudly provides this curriculum as a part of its academic outreach programs in an effort to help inspire and engage the next generation of engineers, scientists, technicians and mathematicians. PTC’s award winning “Engineering of the Future” program has impacted students and teachers all over the world. It is our hope that this new set of curriculum will continue to prepare the next generation of workforce for our customers and help improve the quality of life across the globe.</string>
    <string name="workshop_introduction_advanced_iot">IoT is booming and you hear every day of new wearables, new smart objects, new IoT applications or even new machine learning algorithms to help make sense of data gathered through IoT.
        \nThis workshop helps you catch up the wave of IoT development along with a dynamism of new solutions and applications. It will guide you through the various aspects of IoT, different opportunities and hands on development experiments.
        \nPTC is an acclaimed visionary and industry leader that provides an award winning Industrial IoT (IIoT) solutions platform, Thingworx. The workshop will provide a glimpse into the entire technology stack that enables the industry to build production ready IIoT Application within days. Discover how easy it is build complex industrial applications straddling data collection, visualization and analytics.</string>
    <string name="workshop_introduction_hello_to_hired">This intensive workshop focuses on boosting students’ confidence in cracking the interviews. The tips on effective communication skills, confidence building, resume writing and body language will help them face interviews confidently and express themselves effectively. </string>
    <string name="workshop_introduction_rc_nitro_car">RC Car Workshop provides you the enthralling opportunity to get practical knowledge of actual Car and its designing procedure. You get hands-on expe-rience in installing different component of car and learn down the complete working of car. The designing principles of Car are studied during our RC Car workshops at different parts of India.
        \nIt is a two-days workshop which mainly focuses  from Basics to Advanced concepts in Automobile Engineering. It brings you face to face with the IC En-gine technology while providing you valuable hands-on experience for build-ing your own remote controlled nitro car under the guidance of renowned pro-fessionals.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_introduction_multi_touch_and_gesture_computing">Multi Touch and Gesture Computing workshop is organized by Roboflux. Augmented reality (AR) is a live direct or indirect view of a physical, real-world environment whose elements are "augmented" by computer-generated sensory input such as sound, video, graphics or GPS data. It is related to a more general concept called computer-mediated reality, in which a view of reality is modified (possibly even diminished rather than augmented) by a computer. Don’t miss this opportunity. </string>


    <string name="workshop_content_ethical_hacking">1. Ethical Hacking: Legal or illegal?
        \n• Concepts of Hacking
        \na. Ethical Hacking and Information Security : Definition
        \nb. Who is hacker (Security Expert)?
        \nc. How to become a Hacker?
        \nd. Why do we need hackers?
        \ne. Case Studies: Hackers Methodology and Innovation
        \nf .Difference between hacker and cracker?
        \n• Types of Hackers(As per Knowledge)
        \na. Coders
        \nb. Admins
        \nc. Script Kiddies
        \n• Types of Hackers(As per Working)
        \na. White hat hackers
        \nb. Black hat hackers
        \nc. Grey hat hackers
        \nd. Hacktivists (Cyber Terrorists)
        \n•	How to secure yourself from Attackers
        \n•	How to Stop Attackers
        \n•	Indian Cyber Law
        \na. Real Scenario
        \nb. Types of Cyber Crime
        \nc. Indian IT Act 2000
        \n2. E-Mails: exploitation and Security
        \n•	What is an E-mail
        \n•	Working of E-mail
        \n•	Traveling of an E-Mail
        \n•	Email Servers
        \na. Definition
        \nb. Usage
        \n• E-mail Forgery
        \na. Anonymous Mailing techniques
        \n    Using Websites
        \n    Using Self Developed PHP Script
        \nb. E-Mail Bombers
        \n•  Security to Anonymous Mailing
        \na. Can User stop Receiving Fake Mails?
        \nb. Tracing an Attacker
        \nc. Proving a Fake Mail
        \n•  Attacks on E-Mail Password
        \na. Attackers Anatomy and Psychology while hacking the passwords
        \nb. Technical Attacks
        \n• Using Fake Websites: Phishing
        \n• Keyloggers
        \n• Non-Technical Attacks
        \na. Dumpster Diving
        \nb. Shoulder surfing
        \nc. Social Engineering
        \n•  Securing the E-Mail Passwords
        \na. Password Policies
        \nb. Benefits of SSL Certificate for a User.
        \nc. Anti – Trust Policies
        \n•  Email Forensics
        \na. E-Mail Header Analysis
        \nb. Who is Look Up Query
        \nc. Tracing a Sender of an E-Mail

        \n3. Inside Threats: Operating System Hacking and Secu-rity
        \n• Introduction to System Softwares
        \na. Windows o Ubuntu(Linux)
        \nb. Back Track(Live OS)
        \n• Windows Security Components and Working
        \na. Windows Security Components
        \nb. User  Account Login Process
        \n• Implementation of Virtualization
        \na. VM Ware Workstation
        \nb. Installation and Usage
        \n•	Windows
        \n•	Linux
        \na.Oracle Virtual Box
        \nb.MS Virtual PC
        \nc.Tracing Sender’s IP Address
        \nd.Tracing Sender’s Location
        \n•	Attacks on Windows Login Password
        \na. Resetting Windows login password without the old password
        \nb. Removing Windows login password without the old password
        \n• Other Security Measure
        \na. BIOS User and Supervisory password
        \nb. Biometric
        \nc. Implementing Syskey File Encryption
        \n• Windows Inbuilt Flaws and Security Loopholes
        \na. Hidden Accounts o Backdoor Via Sticky Keys
        \nb. Administrator Escalation on Limited accounts
        \n• Invading into Computer System
        \na. Recovering BIOS Password
        \nb. Recovering Biometric Password
        \nc. Disabling Syskey File Encryption
        \n• Optimizing Windows Computer System
        \na. Steganography
        \nb. Hiding Files behind an Image
        \n• Restrict Hackers into box
        \na. Restricting Access to Files and Folders
        \n•	 ACLs Calculation
        \na. Configuring Strong Password
        \nb. Changing Boot Order
        \nc. BIOS Password
        \nd. Physical Security

        \n4. Malwares: Trojan, Viruses and Worms
        \n•	What are malwares?
        \n•	Trojans
        \na. What is a Trojan?
        \nb. Types of Trojans
        \n• Trojan Attack Methods
        \na. Direct Connection
        \nb. Reverse Connection
        \n•	Some Knows Trojans
        \n•	Detection of Trojan
        \na. Using Anti-Trojan Software
        \nb. Manual Detection
        \n     TCP View
        \n    Process Viewer
        \n   Process Explorer
        \n•	Viruses
        \n•	Working and Functionality of Viruses
        \n•	Development
        \na. Batch Programming
        \nb. Programming
        \n•	Development of Folder lockers
        \n•	Developing Professional Security tools   Compilation and EXE Gen-eration
        \n•	Detection and Manual Removal
        \na. Detecting Viruses
        \nb. Process Monitoring
        \nc. Manual Removal of Viruses

        5.Playing with Networks
        \n• Introduction to the LAN(Local Area  Networks)   What is Network?
        \na. What is networking?
        \nb. Understanding Network Devices
        \nc. Wireless Hacking( Wi-Fi WEP Key Cracking)
        \n        Flaws and Security o Attacks on Networks
        \n           Sniffing
        \n       MITM(ARP Poisoning)
        \n•	Live Demonstration
        \n•	Introduction to the LAN(Local Area Networks)
        \na. What is Network?
        \nb. What is networking?
        \nc. Understanding Network Devices
        \nd. Wireless Hacking( Wi-Fi WEP Key Cracking)
        \n• Flaws and Security
        \na. Attacks on Networks
        \nb. Sniffing
        \nc. MITM(ARP Poisoning)
        \n•	Live Demonstration
        \n•	Secure Network Configuration
        \na. Configuring Anti-Sniffers
        \nb. MAC Filtering Restrictions
        \nc. Configuration of WPA2 Keys
         \n• Introduction to Web Application Security
        \na. What is Web Server
        \nb. What is Database Servers
        \nc. The Web Login Process
        \nd. What is Web application Security
        \ne. Why is Web application Security Important
        \n• Understanding Attack Vectors
        \na. Vulnerabilities and Evolving Threats
        \nb. Exploit Analysis
        \n• Web Application Attacks
        \na.	SQL Injection
        \n          Basic Injection
        \n          Advance Injections
        \nb. Google Dorks – Using Google as an Expert
        \nc. Directory Traversal Attacks
        \n            Sever Side code Retrieval
        \n• Putting breaks on Web Application attacks
        \na. Proper Monitoring
        \nb. Proper Input Validation
        \nc. Deny Google to your Website
        \nd. Finding Backdoors in the Website
        \ne. Secure Programming
        \n•	Mozilla Firefox as a Hacking tool
        \n•	Bypassing Proxy – Intermediate
        \na. What is Proxy
        \nb. Bypassing a Proxy
        \nc. Opening Block Websites
        \nd. Using Google as Proxy

        \n7.Mobile Hacking – VOIP and Android
        \n•	Introduction to Mobile Technology o Operating Systems   Series 60 Nokia
        \nAndroid from Google
        \n•	VOIP – Definition and Usage
        \na. What is VOIP
        \nb. Requirements for Setting up VOIP server
        \n    Asterisk Configuration
        \n    SIP Connections
        \n• Call Forgery
        \na. Call from any number
        \n        Using Soft Phones
        \n                Using Websites
        \n        Using Series 60 mobile Phones
        \n• SMS Forgery
        \na. Sending SMS from any number
        \nb. Attack on Facebook
        \n• Security to Mobile Attacks
        \na. Call Data Records Recognition
        \nb. VOIP Identification
        \nc. Nigerian 419 Scam (Advance Fee Attacks)
        \n• Android
        \na. Running android on Laptops

        \n8.Software Reverse Engineering
        \n•	What is Reverse Engineering
        \n•	Software - Definition
        \n•	Disassembling the Softwares
        \na. Getting the code of EXEs
        \nb. Manipulating the Code of EXEs
        \n• Dis-assemblers and Debuggers
        \na. Olly DBG
        \nb. Windows Dis-assembler
        \n• Software Cracking and Serial Key Phishing
        \na. Analyzing Assembly Code of Software
        \nb. Tracing the Error Message
        \nc. Setting Break Point
        \nd. Stepping the Assembly Code
        \ne. Checking the Registers for the Key
        \n• Software Patching o Disassembling a Software
        \na. Error Tracing
        \nb. Decoding the Instructions
        \nc. Generating Patch to inject the instruction of Running the Patch
        \n• Applying Application Security
        \na. Introduction to Application Encryption
        \nb. Using the Setup Encrypters
        \nc. Applying Strong Serial Key Algorithms
</string>
    <string name="workshop_content_hovercraft">Session 1
        \nTheoretical Session:
        \n·	Lecture on scientific concepts behind Hovercraft
        \n·	Understanding the Physics behind functioning of a Hovercraft
        \n·	Structure and parts of a Hovercraft
        \n·	Introduction to Remote Controlled Hovercraft
        \n·	Electronics used in the design of RC Hovercraft

        \nSession 2
        \n    Design and Brainstorming session:
        \n·	Understanding Design algorithm of hovercrafts
        \n·	Calculation and Hovercraft design evaluation
        \n·	brainstorming for Innovative  RC Hovercraft idea
        \n·	Analysis and implementation of creative hovercraft ideas

        \nSession 3
        \nPratical fabrication session:
        \n·	Fabrication of Hovercraft
        \n·	Installation of electronic hovercraft component’s.
        \n·	Practical Implementation of innovative ideas.
        \n·	Efficiency escalation of Hovercraft
        \n·	Analysis of the hovercraft

        \nSession 4
        \n    Test run:
        \n·	Hovercraft test run
        \n·	handling techniques for hovercraft
        \n·	Explanation of Error in Design
        \n·	Design modification concepts
        \n·	Best Design Selection

        \nHovercraft Workshop Material :
        \n•	Battery
        \n•	Electronic Speed Controller
        \n•	Servo Motor (3 Pieces)
        \n•	Motor
        \n•	Propeller
        \n•	Working Tools
        \n•	Corrugated Air frame
        \n•	Landing Gear
        \n•	Wheels and Accessories
        \n•	Wing Holder
        \n•	Control Rod
        \n•	Clevises
        \n•	Control Horns
    </string>
    <string name="workshop_content_android_app_development">Day - 1 (Introduction to android with basic inputs)
        \n1.	GETTING STARTED
        \no	Formulating idea

        \n2.	ANDROID BASICS
        \no	Introduction and setting up Android Studio.
        \no	Basic Android concepts.

        \n3.	BUILDING LAYOUT
        \no	Introduction to various widgets.
        \no	What are Layouts, Containers, XML?
        \no	Positioning of widgets, playing with views and layout.
        \no	Making UI/UX
        \no	Making a Birthday Card/any other example.

        \n4.	MAKING APP INTERACTIVE
        \no	Introduction to Back-end.
        \no	Writing simple Java statements.
        \no	Incorporating widgets.
        \no	Trigger events

        \nDay – 2 (Networking and Data storage)
        \n1.	NETWORKING
        \no	JSON Parsing
        \no	HTTP Networking
        \no	Threads and parellelism

        \n2.	DATA STORAGE
        \no	SQL
        \no	Shared Preferences
</string>
    <string name="workshop_content_fantastic_four">DAY 1:
        \n    INTRODUCTION TO ROBOTICS
        \n•	What is Robotics?
        \n•	Future of Robotics
         \nUNDERSTANDING ROBOT LOCOMOTION
        \n•	Tracked Robot
        \n•	Biped Robot
        \n•	Wheel Robot
        \n    BASIC ELECTRONICS
        \n•	Basic Components
        \n•	Logic Gates
        \n•	OP-AMP
        \n•	Oscillators
        \n    UNDERSTANDING ACTUATORS
        \n•	DC Motor
        \n•	Stepper Motor
        \n    INTRODUCTION TO MICROCONTROLLER
        \n•	Different Families of Microcontroller
        \n•	Basic Features of Microcontroller

        \n    INTRODUCTION TO ARDUINO/FREEDUINO BOARDS
        \n•	Internal Structure of Arduino
        \n•	Wiring and Programming IDE

        \nDAY 2:
        \n    INTRODUCTION TO ANDROID
        \n•	Introduction to different types of Android Applications
        \n•	Communication between Android Embedded System
        \n•	Introduction to Voice Controlled Robot Application
        \n    INTRODUCTION OF BLUETOOTH MODULE
        \n•	Writing and programming of IDE
        \n•	Basics of Bluetooth
        \n•	Bluetooth connections between to devices
        \n•	Bluetooth module with Arduino
        \n    INTRODUCTION OF PROCESSING
        \n•	Wiring and Programming IDE
        \n    INTRODUCTION TO BLUETOOTH MODULE
        \n•	"TERA TERM SOFTWARE"
        \n•	Serial Communication Between MAT LAB and Microcontroller
        \n    CONNECTING ARDUINO WITH PROCESSING
        \n•	 Serial and Parallel Communication with Arduino
        \n    INTRODUCTION TO L293D (MOTOR DRIVER)
        \n•	Introduction to actuators
        \n•	 Introduction to NPN PNP transistor switching
        \n•	 Working of motors
        \n    CREATING YOUR BLUETOOTH CONTROLLED ROBOT
        \n 1.Assembling
        \n•	Assembling robot and circuitry
        \n        2.Programming
        \n•	Coding : Burning program within microcontroller
        \n•	Testing : Functioning of a Robot
</string>
    <string name="workshop_content_3d_game_designing_and_virtual_reality">SESSION 1:
        \n    Introduction to Virtual Reality
        \na.	Overview
        \nb.	Planning
        \nc.	Technologies
        \n    AUGMENTED REALITY VS VIRTUAL REALITY
        \n    DISPLAY TECHNOLOGIES
        \na.	Head Mounted Display
        \nb.		Contact lenses
        \nc.		Eye Glasses
        \nd.		Handheld devices (Mobiles, Tablets etc.)
        \n    VR Applications
         \n   Software Distribution

        \nSESSION 2:
        \n3D Unity
        \n    Software Installation
        \n    Working on 3d unity
        \n    Basic Functions of 3D Unity
        \n    Basic ball game design using Unity
        \n Advance ball game design using Unity

        \nSESSION 3:
        \n    Designing an environment like “Temple run game”
        \n    Creating Coins with animation
        \n    How to display a score
        \n    Designing sky boxes, mountains, trees, water etc.
        \n    Designing a Virtual Maze game

        \nSESSION 4:
        \n    Virtual Reality Kit distribution
        \n    Virtual Reality Google Headset building
        \n    Demonstration of live VR projects developed by students.
        \n    Zonal Level competition
</string>
    <string name="workshop_content_creo_workshop">Solid Modeling
        \nModel Structure
        \nModel Analysis
        \nAssembly Constraints
        \nAssembling Systems
        \nAssembling Mechanisms
        \nConcept Development
        \nPreliminary Design
        \nCreating Parts and Assemblies
        \nAdvanced Modeling
        \nA Virtual Laboratory
        \nCalculating Stress and Deflection</string>
    <string name="workshop_content_advanced_iot">Day 1
        \nWhat is Internet of Things? (45 min)
        \nIntroduction
        \nIoT Architectures
        \nBuilding IoT Network (75 min)
        \nSensors, Actuators, MEMS
        \nSmart Objects, SANETS, WSNS
        \nConnecting IoT Devices Over Wireless with IEEE 802.15.4
        \nFamily of Protocols, Amendments - ZigBee, LPWANs, LoRaWAN
        \nHome IoT Network – NFC, Bluetooth, WIFI, IPV6 – adaptations
        \nManagement Protocols – CoAP, MQTT, SCADA
        \nSecurity
        \nBeginning of your journey with IoT (Hands –on) (3 hours)
        \nInstructor led step by step project
        \nHardware Setup and Data Collection
        \nOverview of hardware board and companion networking board
        \nHands on with Sensors/Programming
        \nProject with Sensors and data collection
        \nYour journey with IoT (Hands-On) – Making sense of the Data (3 Hours)
        \nIntroduction to PTC ThingWorx IoT Platform – How PTC ThingWorx
        \nsolutions reduce the time, cost, and risk required to build innovative
        \nMachine-to-Machine (M2M) and Internet of Things (IoT) applications
        \nProject - Create remote thing in ThingWorx. Add properties that match with sensors.
        \nBuild an IoT application using the revolutionary Mashup Technology
        \nDay 2
        \nThingworx IIoT Application Demo (1 hour)
        \nYour journey with IoT (Hands-on) - Harnessing the data from IoT Network(2 hours)
        \nThingworx Analytics – Introduction to Anomaly Detection
        \nAnalytics, Big Data, Machine Learning
        \nEdge, Fog Computing
        \nIndustry Applications Overview (1 hour)
        \nManufacturing
        \nTransportation
        \nSmart City
        \nPublic Safety
        \nSelf-propelled exploration projects with IoT (4 hours)
        \nBuild your own IoT project
        \nChoose from curated sample projects
        \nBring your own idea
        \nCollect the Sensors data
        \nBuild IoT Applications using the data.
        \nAnalyze the data from sensors</string>
    <string name="workshop_content_hello_to_hired">Sessions:
        \n1.	Role of Communication Skills’=
        \n2.	Confidence Building
        \n3.	Resume Writing
        \n4.	Interview skills
        \n5.	Body Language and Etiquette
        \n6.	Mock Interviews

        \nThe training involves:
        \na. A pre-course questionnaire
        \nb. Activity-based sessions
        \nc. Mock interviews
        \nd. A post-course questionnaire
        \ne. Certificate to every participant
</string>
    <string name="workshop_content_rc_nitro_car"> 	Complete study of automobile sector and vehicle dynamics
        \n1.	Basics of Automobile
        \n•	What is an automobile?
        \n•	Design of chassis
        \n•	Suspension unit
        \n•	Steering system
        \n•	Transmission system
        \n•	Braking Unit
        \n•	IC engine
        \n2.	Vehicle Dynamics
        \n•	Geometric aspects of automobile
        \n•	Aerodynamic aspects of vehicle
        \n•	Aspects of vehicles related to
        \n•	 Motion
        \n•	Mass and its distribution
        \n    Detailed Study of IC Engine and importance of different parts.
        \n    Different types of RC cars and its components along with methods for fabrication.
        \n       Introduction to latest technology
        \n       Detailed explanation on working of component
        \n       Hands-On session (for individual groups).
        \n       Live demonstration of the internal engine mechanisms
        \n       RC Car Test Run Session
        \n•	Driving session.
        \n•	Maintenance procedure for RC Nitro cars.
        \n•	Detailed Session on controlling RC cars on track.
        \n•	Essential Checks to be done pre and post running RC car.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_content_multi_touch_and_gesture_computing">Day 1:
        \n1.  Introduction to touch screens (Resistive, Capacitive and Optical Touch)
        \n2.  Types of Optical multi-touch screens
        \n3.  Create your own multi-touch pad using web camera
        \n4.  Introduction to Image Processing
        \n5.  Coding to process an image or a video.
        \n6.  Programming to track Blob/Touch.
        \n7.  Control Mouse using camera
        \n8.  Introduction to Reactivision
        \n9.  Fiducial Tracking
        \n10. Code your own media player
        \n11. Play music using a paper
        \n12. Create a virtual Piano/Drum/Guitar
        \n13. Introduction to Motion sensing devices
        \n14. Introduction to Airbar

        \nDay 2:
        \n1. Create Interactive Touch Wall
        \n2. Convert normal laptop screen into touch
        \n3. Control your PC using gestures
        \n4. Introduction to Kinect
        \n5. Create Kinect applications and games
        \n6. Introduction to Virtual Reality
        \n7. Create application for Virtual Reality
        \n8. Introduction to augmented reality
        \n9. Create application for augmented reality
</string>


    <string name="workshop_benefits_ethical_hacking">1.	Certification: Each participant will get a participation certificate.
        \n2.	Newest Softwares at hands.
        \n3.	Doubt Clearing Session for all the students at the end of the Work-shop.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_benefits_hovercraft">• Hands on Sessions by experts.
        \n• Each Participant will Certificate of participation.
        \n• Interactive sessions.
        \n• Doubt Clearing Session for all the students at the end of the workshop.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_benefits_android_app_development">·	Hands on and completely interactive session by experts.
        \n·	Doubt clearing session at the end of workshop.
        \n·	Application development resources will be provided.
        \n·	Opportunity of becoming member of aceshub to work on various related projects of different technology stack.
        \n·	Gifts/goodies from aceshub.
        \n·	Each participant will get certificate.

</string>
    <string name="workshop_benefits_fantastic_four">•	Hands on Sessions by experts.
        \n•	Robotics toolkit will be given in a group of 4-5 students.
        \n•	Each Participant will get ISO Certification.
        \n•	Interactive sessions  with live demo on kits.
        \n•	Doubt Clearing Session for all the students at the end of the Workshop.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_benefits_3d_game_designing_and_virtual_reality">Learn and Interact with IT engineers and get to know basics of Information Technology.
        \nReceive an unparalleled education on the art of building apps and games with personal one – on – one attention.
        \nPowerPoint Presentation, Live Demos
        \nInteractive Questions and Answer session and comprehensive material.
        \nCertification will be provided from RoboKart.com.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_benefits_creo_workshop">After training completion student can develop virtual 3D models of any mechanical component, assembly with detail manufacturing drawing of the same.
        \nGet to work on the latest version of creo, CREO 4.0.
        \nAfter training completion student can utilise this skills for inter college projects.
        \nStudent can work as a CAD/Design Engineer in any Automotive or Manufacturing company.</string>
    <string name="workshop_benefits_advanced_iot">Hands on Sessions by experts in Industry
        \nIoT Kit will be provided to each team
        \nTap physical things into digital world
        \nMonitor and Control physical things from IoT Apps
        \nInteractive sessions with live demo on kits as well as opportunity to build on
        \nyour own ideas
        \nIntroduction and training on PTC award winning IIoT Platform, Thingworx
        \nEach Participant will get Certification.</string>
    <string name="workshop_benefits_hello_to_hired">1.A mock interview session by the experts.
        \n2.Both pre-course and post course questionnaire.
        \n3.Resume writing session.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_benefits_rc_nitro_car"> Hands on Sessions by experts.
 		\nToolkit will be given in a group of 5-6 students.
 		\nEach Participant will get Certificate of participation.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_benefits_multi_touch_and_gesture_computing">1. Build your own gesture controlled applications.
        \n2. Understanding Concept of Image Processing
        \n3. Concept behind media player
        \n4. Well Trained Faculties from Roboflux
        \n5. 100% hands on experience of programming.

</string>


    <string name="workshop_outcome_ethical_hacking">1. Understand computer systems threats
		\n2. Understand the advisory and counter measures
		\n3. Employ basic practical security principles to computer systems 	    and infrastructure.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_outcome_hovercraft">•	Explore the principles behind hovercraft design and science of air-cushion vehicle, ACV with aeromodelling and automobile nuances.
        \n•	Introduction to Design Algorithm of a hovercraft based upon aeromodelling and vehicle dynamics Concepts.
        \n•	Fabricate your own Hovercraft and also get guided to implement your own innovative hovercraft design concepts.
        \n•	Learn about different hovering techniques of hovercrafts by test running your hovercrafts in land and water and enhance your aeromodelling and automobile skills.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_outcome_android_app_development">AT THE END OF THE WORKSHOP, PARTICPANTS WILL HAVE A KNOWLEDGE OF HOW TO GET STARTED FOR DEVELOPING AN APPLICATION FROM SCRATCH AND CONVERTING IDEA ON PAPER TO REALITY.
        \nALSO STUDENTS WILL HAVE AN INSIGHT OF GOOD CODING PRACTISES AND NEW TRENDS IN ANDROID DEVELOPMENT.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_outcome_fantastic_four">AT THE END OF THE WORKSHOP STUDENTS WILL BE ABLE TO MAKE THEIR OWN GESTURE CONTROLLED ROBOT, VOICE CONTROLLED ROBOT, BLUETOOTH CONTROLLED ROBOT, TOUCH SCREEN CON-TROLLED ROBOT AND ANDROID CONTROLLED ROBOT. </string>
    <string name="workshop_outcome_3d_game_designing_and_virtual_reality"> Game design concept and their perspectives
        \nStrong knowledge on Unity 3D Game Engine
        \nSolid introduction to VR and techniques through Vuforia.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_outcome_creo_workshop">◦ Training on Solid Modeling, Model Structure, Model Analysis, Advanced Modeling and many more concepts.
        \n◦ Training programs designed in consultation with industry experts and professionals
        \n◦ Experience on projects
        \n◦ All faculties are Certified by PTC for Creo.</string>
    <string name="workshop_outcome_advanced_iot">Workshop will be first step towards journey of thousand miles in the field of professional IoT development landscape. It will give good overview of domain and future prospects in the field of IoT.</string>
    <string name="workshop_outcome_hello_to_hired">1.Mock interview session will build the confidence of participants.
        \n2.Participants will get to know to how to present themselves in different situations.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_outcome_rc_nitro_car">Complete study of automobile engineering.
         \nDetailed study of IC Engine.
 	     \nStudy of RC Car components and its working procedure.
 	     \nRC car assembly and driving tips.
 	     \nRC nitro engine tuning procedure and maintenance.
</string>
    <string name="workshop_outcome_multi_touch_and_gesture_computing">1.	Understand Gesture computing and its business
        \n2.	Ability to use concepts of Augmented Reality
        \n3.	Ability to use concepts of Touch Computing
    </string>

    <string name="workshop_venue_ethical_hacking">1. College of Engineering, Pune
			\n2. Aurangabad
</string>
    <string name="workshop_venue_hovercraft">College of Engineering, Pune</string>
    <string name="workshop_venue_android_app_development">College of Engineering, Pune</string>
    <string name="workshop_venue_fantastic_four">1. College of Engineering, Pune
			\n2. Kolhapur
</string>
    <string name="workshop_venue_3d_game_designing_and_virtual_reality">College of Engineering, Pune</string>
    <string name="workshop_venue_creo_workshop">College of Engineering, Pune</string>
    <string name="workshop_venue_advanced_iot">College of Engineering, Pune</string>
    <string name="workshop_venue_hello_to_hired">College of Engineering, Pune</string>
    <string name="workshop_venue_rc_nitro_car">Shri Guru Gobind Singhji Institute of Engineering and Technology, Nanded. </string>
    <string name="workshop_venue_multi_touch_and_gesture_computing">BATU, Lonere</string>


    <string name="workshop_fees_ethical_hacking">₹ 1100 /- per participant</string>
    <string name="workshop_fees_hovercraft">: ₹ 1100 /- per participant</string>
    <string name="workshop_fees_android_app_development"><![CDATA[<p>₹ 1100 /- <b>per participant</b></p>]]></string>
    <string name="workshop_fees_fantastic_four">₹ 1100 /- per participant </string>
    <string name="workshop_fees_3d_game_designing_and_virtual_reality">₹ 1100 /- per participant </string>
    <string name="workshop_fees_creo_workshop">₹ 1100 /- per participant</string>
    <string name="workshop_fees_advanced_iot">₹ 1100 /- per participant</string>
    <string name="workshop_fees_hello_to_hired">₹ 600 /- per participant</string>
    <string name="workshop_fees_rc_nitro_car">₹ 1100 /- per participant</string>
    <string name="workshop_fees_multi_touch_and_gesture_computing">₹1100/- per participant. </string>


    <string name="workshop_date_ethical_hacking">1. 16th and 17th September (Pune).
			\n2. 9th and 10th September (Aurangabad).
</string>
    <string name="workshop_date_hovercraft">16th and 17th September</string>
    <string name="workshop_date_android_app_development">16th and 17th September.</string>
    <string name="workshop_date_fantastic_four">1. 16th and 17th September (Pune).
			\n2. 9th and 10th September (Kolhapur).
</string>
    <string name="workshop_date_3d_game_designing_and_virtual_reality">16th and 17th September</string>
    <string name="workshop_date_creo_workshop">16th and 17th September.</string>
    <string name="workshop_date_advanced_iot">16th and 17th September.</string>
    <string name="workshop_date_hello_to_hired">16th and 17th September.</string>
    <string name="workshop_date_rc_nitro_car">29th and 30th July.</string>
    <string name="workshop_date_multi_touch_and_gesture_computing">9th-10th September 2017 </string>

</resources>
